Academia Sinica
中央研究院
Academia Sinica 11 six copies
中央研究院 11 6部
Machine Feast Lecture Begins
機械の饗宴講義が始まります
We ask Vice President Chen Jianren to host for us
陳建仁副総統に司会をお願いします。
Director Liu Hudong
劉湖東所長
And some of our academicians here
そしてここにいる学者の何人かは
and ladies and gentlemen
そして紳士淑女の皆様
good night everyone
おやすみなさい、皆さん
today we are very happy
今日私たちはとても幸せです
This knowledge feast of our Academia Sinica
私たちの中央研究院のこの知識の饗宴
I can invite Director Liu Hudong
劉胡東監督をお招きできます
Come talk to us about the topic
このトピックについて話しに来てください
speech
スピーチ
So today is our admission to the Central South Hospital
さて、今日は中南病院への入院です
This knowledge misses the record
この知識は記録に残らない
one day
ある日
Because we have more than 300 applicants today
今日は300名以上の応募者がいるから
Then more than 100 colleagues from our hospital participated
その後、当院から100名以上の同僚が参加しました
Then there are 200 people outside the hospital
病院の外には200人がいる
So wait a minute for those who are too late to come in
遅すぎる人はちょっと待ってください
There are other lecture halls where you can listen to lectures
他にも講義が聴ける講堂あり
So say we
だから私たちはこう言います
Director Liu is very attractive
リュー監督はとても魅力的です
first of all, let's keep it simple
まず第一に、シンプルにしましょう
introduce
導入
Director Liu Budong
監督 劉武東
Liu Yanshi's qualifications
劉燕石の資格
Academician Liu Budong
学者の劉武東
He graduated from the Chemistry Department of National Taiwan University in 1970
1970年に国立台湾大学化学科を卒業
Made in the United States in 1976
1976年にアメリカで作られた
Ph.D. in Chemistry, University of Chicago
シカゴ大学化学博士号取得
He then served
その後彼は奉仕した
Postdoctoral Researcher in Chemistry and Immunology
化学および免疫学の博士研究員
Then go to the famous Scripps in the United States
それからアメリカの有名なスクリップスへ行きます
Research center
リサーチセンター
serve
仕える
La Jolla Medical Research Institute
ラホーヤ医学研究所
research work
研究活動
That's rare
それは珍しいですね
ah
ああ
this one at the time
これは当時の
Dr. Liu is our present Liu Yansi
劉博士は私たちの現在の劉延思です。
also during this period
この期間中も
He once studied at McAnney University in the United States
彼はかつて米国のマッカニー大学に留学したことがある
This one achieved an MD
この人は医学博士を持っています。
UCSD
UCSD
Receive specialist training in dermatology
皮膚科の専門研修を受ける
So he went from chemistry to medical dermatology
そこで彼は化学から皮膚科に進みました
Then he was at this Scripps research center
それから彼はこのスクリップス研究センターにいました
Bannon Associate Professor and Director, Department of Allergy Research
バノン准教授兼アレルギー研究部長
Then at the Allergy-Level Academy of Fine Arts in La Jolla
その後、ラホーヤにあるアレルギーレベルの美術アカデミーで
Professor and Director of the Department of Allergy
教授兼アレルギー科部長
In 2001, he was in the Daishi School in California, USA
2001年、アメリカ・カリフォルニア州の大師学校にて
Professor and Director of Dermatology
皮膚科教授兼院長
2011 as
2011年として
This particular professor at U.C. Davis
カリフォルニア大学デービス校のこの特定の教授
And is now an honorary professor at U.C. Davis
そして現在はカリフォルニア大学デービス校の名誉教授です
The reason is because we are lucky
理由は、私たちは幸運だからです
Academia Sinica in 2011
2011 年の中央研究院
Can invite our director Liu Fudong
当社ディレクターのLiu Fudongを招待できます
Mr. Liu
劉さん
Return to China to serve as the director of our biomedical institute
中国に戻り、生物医学研究所の所長に就任
I am a specific researcher
私は特定の研究者です
We also congratulate Director Yuan
袁監督にもお祝いを申し上げます
This year he was elected as an academician of Academia Sinica
今年、彼は中央研究院の会員に選出されました。
actually
実際
Director Yuan's research on allergy
袁所長とアレルギー研究
Already well-known internationally
すでに世界的に有名な
and made a lot of contributions
そして多くの貢献をしてきました
For example, he has developed
たとえば、彼が開発したのは、
can continuously separate IgE
継続的にIgEを分離できる
is one per globulin
グロブリンごとに 1 つです
At the beginning, I looked at the fusion game package strain
はじめに、フュージョンゲームのパッケージ株を見てみました
it's quite outstanding
それは非常に優れています
in addition
加えて
Director Yuan is studying the coagulation number of galactose
袁所長はガラクトースの凝固数を研究中
you can listen to this part
この部分を聞くことができます
also feet
足も
also sour
酸っぱい
After he returns to our Academia Sinica
彼が中央研究院に戻った後
Already with our biomedical institute
すでに私たちの生物医学研究所と提携しています
and his colleagues in the Central Research Area
中央研究領域の同僚たちと
promoted many large-scale studies together
多くの大規模研究を一緒に推進した
including the relationship between gardens and disease
庭と病気の関係も含めて
That's today's topic
それが今日のテーマです
There is also the part of Tang's biomedicine
唐の生物医学の部分もあります
Director Yuan is also presiding over Taiwan's
袁監督は台湾の
Establishment of Biobank
バイオバンクの設立
with a very important impetus
非常に重要なきっかけで
Taiwan Biomedical Research
台湾生物医学研究
and a job in the development of the biomedical industry
生物医学産業の発展に関わる仕事
That amount of shortening has served as a journal that is well-known abroad
あれだけ短くしたことで海外でも有名な雑誌になった
The Journal of Clinical Investigation
臨床研究ジャーナル
Associate Editor, Jonathan Crane Co. Investigation
Jonathan Crane Co. 調査副編集長
And now it's famous
そして今では有名になりました
The Journal of Dermatology
皮膚科学ジャーナル
Editor-in-Chief of Jonathan Taurogyk's Science
Jonathan Taurogyk's Science 編集長
Of course Academician Liu has won numerous awards
もちろん、Liu アカデミー会員は数々の賞を受賞しています
which also includes this
これも含めて
University of California
カリフォルニア大学
John O. M. Tinger Memorial Award
ジョン・O・M・ティンジャー記念賞
He gave a cancer and lung disease research
彼は癌と肺疾患の研究を行った
this award
この賞
And it is our Taiwan dermatology department
それが私たちの台湾皮膚科です
A very important award from the Society of Dermatology
皮膚科学会からの非常に重要な賞
Professor Li Yaoqing's Memorial Award
李耀青教授記念賞
Also an honorary member of our Taiwan Dermatology Association
台湾皮膚科学会の名誉会員でもあります
Today we are very happy to invite Chief Luo to talk to us about
今日は、ルオ長官をお招きして、次のことについてお話いただけることを大変うれしく思います。
Today's keynote address Response and Disease
本日の基調講演「反応と病気」
Is he our enemy or our friend
彼は私たちの敵ですか、それとも友人ですか
a relationship
関係
that was a great speech
素晴らしいスピーチでした
let us all applaud him
みんなで彼を称賛しましょう
Thank you, Dean Shengfu, for your introduction
Dean Shengfu さん、ご紹介いただきありがとうございます
Thank you everyone, it's raining today
みなさん、ありがとうございます、今日は雨です
listen to the speech here
ここでスピーチを聞いてください
I am very very happy to have this opportunity
このような機会を頂けてとてもとても嬉しいです
share with you
あなたと分け合う
My response to this inflammatory response and disease
この炎症反応と病気に対する私の反応
some understanding of the relationship
関係性についてのある程度の理解
I'm doing research
研究をしています
Just now Dean Shengfu also mentioned that it is immune
ちょうど今、ディーン・シェンフも免疫があると言いました
Also very interested in the response to the speech
スピーチへの反応も非常に興味深い
In this regard, professional speeches have given
この点に関して、専門家の講演では、
Quite many times, but the words of popular science is the first time
何度もあるが、大衆科学の言葉は初めてだ
Then I know I saw the statistics of this registration
その後、この登録の統計を見たことがわかりました
Many of them are business related
その多くはビジネス関連です
I hope I'm not overly simplistic.
あまり単純化しすぎないことを祈ります。
that's not for that
それはそのためではない
It's also a stranger
それも見知らぬ人です
That hopefully speaking can be understood
うまくいけば話が理解できるようになります
then some gain
それからいくらかの利益
the word that speaks
話す言葉
In fact, it has been known for two thousand years
実は2000年も前から知られていたんです
That's when you speak
それはあなたが話すときです
it's a latin word called
と呼ばれるラテン語です
set to fire is to set fire to burn
set to fire は火をつけて燃やすことです
Then this is the word inflame
それからこれは炎症という言葉です
In fact, almost a century ago
実は1世紀近く前に
almost 150 years ago
約150年前
Only then did the concept of that cell come in
そのとき初めて、その細胞の概念が登場しました
put in this speech response
このスピーチの応答を入力してください
Then you know how to speak and respond
そうすれば、話し方や返答の仕方がわかります
Probably how to continue to start some
おそらく、いくつかを開始し続ける方法
Some of that new development understands
その新たな展開の一部は理解できます
but so of course
でも当然です
So this statement response is not an update
したがって、このステートメント応答は更新ではありません
But what about the disease?
しかし、病気についてはどうでしょうか？
is relatively new
比較的新しいです
It's something that happened in the last twenty or thirty years
それはここ20年か30年の間に起こった出来事です
found that many diseases
多くの病気が見つかった
can be explained by speech
音声で説明できる
The disease used to be thought to be caused by something other than inflammation
この病気は炎症以外の何かによって引き起こされると考えられていました
Does the inflammation have something to do with the inflammation now?
今の炎症と何か関係があるのでしょうか？
So today I will focus on the topic of inflammation.
そこで今日は炎症に焦点を当てたいと思います。
with disease
病気で
The first one to use this is a simple 30-second cartoon
最初にこれを使用するのは、シンプルな 30 秒の漫画です
It's from Google
Google からのものです
That's what I think is inflammation towards this polarity
それがこの極性への炎症だと思います
I think it is a very simple and clear explanation
とてもシンプルで分かりやすい説明だと思います
Then you see this is a capillary
そうすると、これが毛細血管であることがわかります
and then there is that blood
そしてその血があります
It's the red iron ball that will flow through
流れるのは赤い鉄球
sometimes white blood cells
時々白血球
And then you'll find bacteria coming in
そして、細菌が入ってくるのがわかります
It's like a skin
まるで皮膚のようだ
After bacteria enter under the skin
細菌が皮膚の下に侵入した後
The bacteria also signal to make the microvascular cells
細菌はまた、微小血管細胞を作るように信号を送ります
This time it is closed cells
今回はクローズドセルです
it will react
それは反応するだろう
then here
それからここで
Substances in the blood come out
血液中の物質が出てくる
Then the next step is to let the blood vessels
次のステップは、血管を拡張することです。
The other information is that its white blood cells will come out
もう一つの情報は、白血球が出てくるということです。
Well, those are red blood cells, you can see that
そうですね、それらは赤血球です、ご覧のとおりです
Here comes the bacteria
ここに細菌がやって来ます
Then it emits some signal
その後、何らかの信号を発します
The signal that the blood vessel knows will make some changes in the future
血管が知っている信号が将来何らかの変化を起こす
Then here, some of its blood vessels
それから、ここにその血管の一部が
Some liquid still escapes
一部の液体がまだ漏れています
What about some substances in these bands?
これらのバンド内のいくつかの物質はどうでしょうか?
Combined with that bacteria
その細菌と結合すると、
generate some more signals
さらに信号を生成する
Then this one will come out
そしたらこれが出てくるよ
it starts eating the cells
細胞を食べ始めます
And the bacteria is clear here
ここではバクテリアが透明です
That's the acute origin reaction.
それが急性原発反応です。
So the definition of origin reaction
したがって、原点反応の定義は
That is to say, the biological tissue is traumatized, internally injured
つまり、生体組織は外傷を受け、内部が損傷されます。
or patient infection
または患者の感染
Like just now, it was an example of a patient being infected
先ほどと同様、患者が感染した例でした
or reaction to exposure to irritating substances
または刺激性物質への曝露に対する反応
Then its tissue response is to include the red
次に、その組織反応には赤色が含まれます。
Fever Pain Symptoms
発熱、痛みの症状
The reason for the redness is that the microvessels will expand
赤みの原因は微小血管が拡張するためです
Then the blood is more expensive
そうすると血液の値段が高くなる
That's because blood is red
それは血が赤いからです
so it will have shallots
エシャロットが入っているので
The tissue color of that part compares with red
その部分の組織の色は赤と比較されます
In general, it is because the substances in the blood will escape from what I just said.
一般的には、今言ったような血液中の物質が逃げてしまうからです。
If you have a fever, it is also related to blood circulation.
熱がある場合は血行も関係しています。
it's ours
それは私たちのものです
cold body temperature
冷たい体温
It spreads into the so-called injured tissue
いわゆる損傷組織に広がります
If there is pain, it is after these substances come out
痛みがある場合はこれらの物質が出た後です
it affects the nerve endings
神経終末に影響を与える
So in this following speech
したがって、この次のスピーチでは
I'll talk about it first
まずそれについて話します
It is the relationship between avoiding the source and the inflammatory response
原因の回避と炎症反応の関係です
then talk about trauma
それからトラウマについて話す
Then talk about some irritating substances
次に、いくつかの刺激性物質について話します
Then talk about internal injuries
それから内部損傷について話します
but some
しかし、いくつかの
For example, related to the heart
例えば、心臓に関係するものです。
related to angels
天使に関係するもの
so high cool range
非常に高いクール範囲
is brutal
残忍です
our human body
私たちの人間の体
not actually a human body
実際には人間の体ではありません
Even the D-Dent animals are the same
D-Dentの動物も同じです
just have this kind of resistance
この種の抵抗を持っているだけです
A mechanism of Defense
防御のメカニズム
like our country
私たちの国のように
If there are foreign enemies
外敵がいると
we will know how to resist
私たちは抵抗する方法を知るでしょう
This is the mechanism of resistance
これが抵抗のメカニズムです
depends on some immune system
何らかの免疫システムに依存する
So the immune response is closely related to the inflammatory response
つまり、免疫反応は炎症反応と密接に関係しているのです。
There are two immune responses
免疫反応には2つあります
an innate immune system
自然免疫システム
One is a response called adaptation
一つは適応と呼ばれる反応です
Let me not mention it for now
今は言及しないでおこう
innate immune words
自然免疫の言葉
The two protagonists are Nutriphil and Microphage
二人の主人公はニュートリフィルとマイクロファージ
This is the missing white blood cell
これは失われた白血球です
Megalithic cells
巨石細胞
The missing white snowball
消えた白い雪玉
in the blood
血の中で
You just saw that cartoon
あなたはちょうどその漫画を見ました
That is the missing white snowball coming out
それは欠けている白い雪玉が出てくることです
it's in the blood
それは血の中にある
Of course, red blood cells are the most
もちろん赤血球が一番多いのですが、
But the most white blood cells are
しかし、白血球の中で一番多いのは、
It is Nilchffville
ニルチフヴィルです
missing white snowball
白い雪玉がなくなった
It is about one and a half times the size of a red blood cell
赤血球の約1.5倍の大きさです
it is a microscope image
顕微鏡画像です
If after dyeing
染めた後なら
You can see it has
あることがわかります
it has several nuclei
核がいくつかある
About five slices of three slices
3枚切り5枚くらい
why is it called neutral
なぜ中立と呼ばれるのか
That's because when dyed
それは染めるときに
Some cells are stained to become stained
一部の細胞は染色されるように染色されます
some cells turn red
一部の細胞が赤くなります
That is, Basophil has Synophil
つまり、好塩基球にはシノフィルがあるということです。
Then this is without Balve
それから、これはバルベなしです
no no no no dyeing
いやいやいや染まらない
not red
赤くない
it is equal to say neutral color
中間色と言うのと同じです
So it's called Nilchffville
だからニルチフビルって言うんだよ
Then it was shown in the cartoon just now
そしたらさっき漫画でも出てきましたよ
It's Nilchffville that circulates in the blood
血の中を巡るのはニルチフヴィル
Then when you get this signal
この信号を受信すると
It will leave the tissue from the blood circulation to dels
組織を血液循環からデルスに残します
At this time, there is a factor called driving factor
このとき、駆動要因と呼ばれる要因があります。
Chimokai
就Chimokai
It is very important in this inflammatory response
この炎症反応において非常に重要です
So I'm researching and researching addicts in this research
そこで私はこの研究で中毒者について調査し研究しています
It will mention several cells
いくつかの細胞について言及します
most important
最も重要な
a few cells
いくつかの細胞
several molecules
いくつかの分子
Molecule is an important thing called Chimokai
分子は知モ怪という大切なもの
So the driving factor
したがって、推進要因は
No need to know the details
詳細を知る必要はありません
But I know that this protein
しかし、私はこのタンパク質が
because of its relationship
その関係性のせいで
Where will this white blood cell come out?
この白血球はどこから出てくるのでしょうか？
know where to go
どこに行くべきか知っています
then it just
それならただ
it's to this germy place
この生臭い場所へです
Then it will put the germ
そうすると雑菌が入るよ
or swallow it
またはそれを飲み込む
or put it
またはそれを置きます
kill that
それを殺してください
or it sucks it
それとも最悪だ
there is a way
やり方がある
But its end result is that it will
しかし、その最終的な結果は、
it is against the germ
それは細菌に対してです
And finally eliminate the germs
そして最後に細菌を除去します
so this is
それでこれは
This is a
これは
in the inflammatory response
炎症反応では
A very important cell is New Nufel
非常に重要なセルはNew Nufelです
This V6 is quite interesting
このV6はかなり面白いです
quite famous now
今ではかなり有名になった
This is Snowball
これはスノーボールです
This is the red snowball
これは赤い雪だるまです
There's a New Nufel in here
ここに新しいニューフェルがあります
those are bacteria
それらは細菌です
Then he will know where the germs are
そうすれば彼は細菌がどこにあるかを知るでしょう
He has been checking this bacteria
彼はこの細菌を検査してきた
and finally swallow it
そして最後に飲み込む
that is not yet
それはまだです
right
右
slowly
ゆっくり
And now he finally got this bacterium in
そして今、彼はついにこの細菌を体内に入れました
exists inside
中に存在する
Then he found another
それから彼は別のものを見つけました
Seems to be bigger bacteria
バクテリアが大きくなったような気がする
he used to devour it
彼はそれをむさぼり食っていた
so this is
それでこれは
That is, he has this real function
つまり、彼はこの本当の役割を持っています
That's the first protagonist
それが最初の主人公です
The second protagonist is the microphage
2人目の主役はマイクロファージ
megalithic cells
巨石細胞
so is this
これもそうです
It will eat the source of the disease
病気の根源を食べてくれる
and after eating
そして食べた後
Same with Newfel in the world
世界の新しいニューフィールドも同様
I didn't say it just now
今言ったんじゃないよ
it has a
それは
There are some called dragon body
竜体と呼ばれるものもある
It will finally eat the source of the disease
ついには病気の根源を食べることになる
break it down
それを壊す
products of decomposition it will come out
分解生成物が出てきます
So in terms of this role of resisting the patient
したがって、患者に抵抗するというこの役割に関しては、
Neutral field is similar to migrophox
中性フィールドはミグロフォックスに似ています
it can eat it too
それも食べられるよ
It can also secrete some substances
何らかの物質を分泌することもあります
kill these bacteria
これらの細菌を殺す
there is a difference
違いがあります
wait a minute i'll talk more
ちょっと待ってください、もっと話します
But the difference is that it
しかし、違うのは、
Because after this decomposition
なぜなら、この分解後は
it is carried out in detail
細かく行われている
I don't think so
私はそうは思わない
But in the end it was able to make that
しかし、最終的にはそれを実現することができました
I just mentioned that there is innate immunity
先ほど自然免疫があると言いましたが、
Immunity to the adaptive response
適応反応に対する免疫
it will make that adaptive response
それは適応的な反応をするでしょう
immune response will come out
免疫反応が出てくる
wait a minute
ちょっと待って
basically
基本的
These are the two neutral fields
これらは 2 つの中立フィールドです
with migrophox
ミグロフォックスと
They are the two protagonists doing the inflammatory response
彼らは炎症反応を起こしている 2 人の主人公です
So here the words
それで、ここで言葉を
It is said that the inflammatory reaction is the enemy or there is
炎症反応が敵なのか、あるのかと言われていますが、
It's obvious here
ここで明らかです
Because if you don't have these inflammatory reactions
なぜなら、これらの炎症反応がなければ、
Without this neutrophil, without microphage
この好中球がなければ、マイクロファージがなければ
If there is a bacterial infection, there is no way to resist it.
細菌感染がある場合、それに抵抗する方法はありません。
So this is an indispensable resistance mechanism of the human body
つまり、これは人体の不可欠な抵抗メカニズムです
Then this resistance mechanism reflects an inflammatory response
そして、この抵抗メカニズムは炎症反応を反映しています。
Another source of disease is the virus
もう一つの病気の原因はウイルスです
Viruses are slightly different
ウイルスは少し異なります
The virus is when the human body knows that there is a virus infection
ウイルスとは、人体がウイルス感染があることを認識することです。
It has a polar cell
極細胞がある
wait a minute i'll talk more
ちょっと待ってください、もっと話します
So let's not talk about the polar cells for now.
したがって、今は極細胞については話さないようにしましょう。
it makes two lymphocytes
2つのリンパ球を作ります
One for T cells and one for B cell activation
1 つは T 細胞用、もう 1 つは B 細胞活性化用
T cells then produce some cytokines
その後、T細胞はいくつかのサイトカインを産生します
I just talked about I just talked about a few cells
私はちょうどいくつかの細胞について話したと言いました
and then several substances
そしていくつかの物質
I just said that KIMOKAI is called the driving factor
キモカイが原動力と先ほど言いました
Cytokines
サイトカイン
These two are the most important two in the inflammatory response
この 2 つは炎症反応において最も重要な 2 つです
two ophthalmia
2つの眼科
cytokines and cytokines
サイトカインとサイトカイン
One is KIMOKAI and the other is cellular liver
1つはKIMOKAI、もう1つは細胞肝臓です。
additionally activated cells
さらに活性化された細胞
T cells produce cytokines
T細胞はサイトカインを産生します
In addition, it knows when there is a virus infection
さらに、ウイルス感染が発生したことを知ることができます
it becomes a cell body
細胞体になります
it kills other cells
他の細胞を殺します
Viruses usually go inside cells
ウイルスは通常細胞内に侵入します
survive there
そこで生き残る
it can breed here
ここで繁殖できる
then there came out
それから出てきました
This cell will know to say
この細胞は言うことを知っているでしょう
where is this virus
このウイルスはどこにありますか
Then it poisons the cell
そして細胞に毒を与えます
virus infected cells
ウイルスに感染した細胞
So use this way to fight this virus
このウイルスと戦うにはこの方法を使用してください
Another way is to use B cells
もう一つの方法はB細胞を使用することです
B cells produce body
B細胞が体を作る
can synthesize virus
ウイルスを合成できる
So just said three
だから今3つ言いました
One is Neutral Fuel and Magavage
1つはニュートラル燃料とマグバッジです
Two to fight the pathogen
病原体と戦う二人
The other is to use 08 ball
もう一つは、08ボールを使用することです。
08 cells to fight the virus
ウイルスと戦う08細胞
These are also immune responses
これらも免疫反応です
But it is also possible to produce
でも生産することも可能です
A basic process of the inflammatory response
炎症反応の基本的なプロセス
good
良い
That's what I just said
それが私が今言ったことです
It's the inflammatory response that we have
それは私たちが抱えている炎症反応です
we can't do without these
これらなしではやっていけません
inflammatory response cells
炎症反応細胞
or these bases
またはこれらの基地
Or that Kimokansalokan
あるいはあのキモカンサロカン
Then I believe in the following one
それなら私は次のことを信じます
I think it's a very good example of an inflammatory response.
これは炎症反応の非常に良い例だと思います。
That is Injury Repair
それが怪我の修復です
That's after the wound
それは傷の後です
how do we get it back
どうやって取り戻しますか
That's because I'm a dermatologist
皮膚科医だから
so i believe
だから私は信じます
The example I chose is also related to the skin
私が選んだ例も肌に関するものです
more familiar
もっと身近な
So the mechanism of wound repair
傷の修復の仕組みは
Generally speaking
一般的に言えば
after being injured
怪我をした後
It can be roughly divided into three stages
大きく3つの段階に分けることができます
let the wound heal
傷を治しましょう
The first stage is Information
最初の段階は情報です
so when you get hurt
だから傷ついたときは
Of course we know that said wounds have wounds
もちろん、その傷には傷があることは知っています
But the first reaction is the inflammatory reaction
しかし、最初の反応は炎症反応です
is an inflammatory reaction
炎症反応です
This is a local inflammatory reaction
これは局所的な炎症反応です
I'll talk about the details later
詳細については後ほどお話します
This is on the first day and the second day
こちらは1日目と2日目です
is a local inflammatory reaction
局所的な炎症反応です
Then there will be a process of cell proliferation
その後、細胞増殖のプロセスが起こります
Then finally the wound presynthesis matures
そして最終的に創傷前合成が成熟します
This is about a week or so
ここ一週間くらいですかね
A week or two here
ここで1〜2週間
But in fact it sometimes
でも実際には時々
If the wound is large, it can be repaired in it for a year.
傷が大きい場合は1年程度で修復可能です。
and then again and again
そして何度も何度も
let it finally mature
いよいよ熟成させます
so here
それでここで
The first is if
1つ目は、
here is a skin
ここにスキンがあります
got hurt
傷ついた
so hurt
とても傷ついた
Of course the first feeling is
もちろん最初の気持ちは
So it should be seen that there is a suspension of school
だから学校は休校になると見るべきだ
Next, when I study abroad in human body
次は人間の体で留学するとき
The school version will come
学校版も来るよ
After the school version came in
学校版が登場してから
Let's learn from the adjacent bone
隣の骨から学ぼう
So that's our body's first reaction
それが私たちの体の最初の反応です
This is not an inflammatory reaction
これは炎症反応ではありません
But in fact the school version will also
しかし、実際には学校バージョンでも
also co-builds the inflammatory response
炎症反応も同時に構築します
I won't mention it anymore
もうそれについては言及しません
Those two are the students of the school version
この二人は学校版の生徒です
what's next
次は何ですか
That means there are germs coming in.
つまり雑菌が入ってくるということです。
Then you might say
そうしたら、あなたはこう言うかもしれません
I actually wash my hands
実は手を洗います
Although after the cut
カット後ですが
There should be no virus
ウイルスなんて存在しないはずだ
but it's really amazing
でも本当にすごいです
is our human body
私たちの人間の体は
you don't know
あなたは知りません
But let's say that the skin is not above
しかし、皮膚がその上にないとしましょう
There are thousands of diseases
何千もの病気がある
the bacteria is on it
細菌が付着している
is quite okay with us
私たちには全然大丈夫です
we don't interfere with them
私たちは彼らに干渉しません
they don't bother us
彼らは私たちを悩ませません
commercial bacteria
市販の細菌
it doesn't infect us
私たちには感染しません
it's over there
あちらにあります
We correspond to co-existence
共存に対応
Usually we don't even know
通常、私たちも知りません
but when hurt
でも傷ついたときは
These germs will enter the human body
これらの細菌は人体に侵入します
At this time we will react
この時点で反応します
just like our first cartoon
私たちの最初の漫画のように
After some bacteria come in
何らかの細菌が侵入してから
White blood cells know how to kill the germs
白血球は細菌を殺す方法を知っています
So it's the same here
だからここも同じだよ
Invading germs attract white blood cells
侵入した細菌が白血球を引き寄せる
white blood cells first neutrophils
白血球 最初の好中球
It is neutrophil
好中球です
So this is the first day
ということで今日が初日です
It's neutrophil coming
好中球が来てるよ
These neutrophils begin to clear these bacteria
これらの好中球はこれらの細菌を除去し始めます
You see less and less bacteria
細菌の数がどんどん減っていきます
mid term
中期
It's called monocytes coming in here
ここに来るのは単球と呼ばれます
Then it becomes true after monocyte activation
単球活性化後にそれは真になります
megalithic cells
巨石細胞
This is MACOFIG
マコフィグです
Its predecessor is the monocyte
その前身は単球です
called MALASIDE
マラサイドと呼ばれる
And then it can also help the gluteal stone invade the bacteria
そして、臀部結石が細菌に侵入するのを助けることもあります
and dead tissue and blood cells
死んだ組織と血球
That's monocytes
それは単球です
So in a few days or so
それで数日以内に
monocytes come in
単球が入ってくる
It then activates into a megalithic cell
その後活性化して巨石細胞となる
Here MACOFIG
ここにマコフィグ
Then it goes on NUGIFILM
それからNUGIFILMに続きます
unfinished work
未完成の仕事
And NUGIFILM died too
そしてNUGIFILMも死んだ
it can swallow it up
それは飲み込むことができる
I'll talk to you next time
次回お話します
not that relevant
あまり関係ない
it always pre-cores
常にプリコアです
Pre-core is to fill in the missing tissue
プレコアは欠損した組織を埋めるものです
and pull into the sides of the wound
そして傷の側面を引っ張ります
Tissue that helps prenucleate to form eight scars
8つの瘢痕を形成する前核化を助ける組織
That's where the words are keratinocytes
そこが言葉のケラチノサイトです
It still needs to be repaired here
ここはまだ修理が必要です
At this time, fibroblasts
このとき、線維芽細胞は、
FIREBLAZE plays an important role
FIREBLAZEは重要な役割を果たします
it secretes
それは分泌する
collagen , fibroelastin
コラーゲン、フィブロエラスチン
These words are here
これらの言葉はここにあります
The wound can close him
傷は彼を閉じることができる
In other words, toe cells
つまり、足指の細胞
This wound must also be pre-closed
この傷も事前に閉じておく必要があります
he moves and proliferates
彼は動き、増殖する
Then here, the wound gets smaller and smaller
そしてここで傷はどんどん小さくなっていきます
In the end, it couldn't be seen that there was a wound
結局傷は見えなかった
so this is
それでこれは
In the end, the sawtooth cell will still be here
結局、鋸歯状細胞はまだここにあるだろう
haven't left yet
まだ出発していません
He continues to put some
彼は続けていくつかを置きます
dead cells, debris
死んだ細胞、破片
and some excess scar tissue
および余分な瘢痕組織
fix it again
もう一度修正してください
It's like doing clean up work here
ここで清掃作業をしているようなものです
so this is a
これは
just a really good one
本当に良いものばかりです
example of an inflammatory response
炎症反応の例
So this is also, we say that the inflammatory reaction is in it
これも炎症反応があると言います
are we have or low
持っているのか、それとも少ないのか
should be there
そこにいるはずです
Because if there is no inflammatory response,
なぜなら、炎症反応がなければ、
The wound is not big
傷は大きくない
So it is a wound that needs to be pre-nucleated, starting with the inflammatory response
したがって、炎症反応から始めて、事前に核除去する必要がある傷です。
That's why there is this step by step like this
だからこそ、このようなステップバイステップがあるのです
to the final pre-core
最後のプリコアまで
But if there is no word in the previous paragraph
ただし、前の段落に単語がない場合は、
It is more difficult to pre-nucleate the wound if it is inflamed.
創傷が炎症を起こしている場合、創核を事前に除去することはより困難です。
But the mechanism of this immunity
しかし、この免疫の仕組みは
Inflammation mechanisms also take a toll
炎症メカニズムも損害を与える
That's because it's hard to say how much is enough, right?
というのは、どのくらいあれば十分なのかを言うのは難しいですよね？
It's what we know we must have an inflammatory response
それは私たちが炎症反応を起こしているに違いないことを知っていることです
To be able to resist the virus from outside
外部からのウイルスに対抗できるようになる
Pre-nucleation requires an inflammatory response
核形成前には炎症反応が必要です
But it's really hard to know how much is enough
でも、どれくらいあれば十分なのかを知るのは本当に難しいです
that's not perfect
それは完璧ではありません
So I now have an example
それで、今例があります
It is when the inflammatory response should have helped the host
炎症反応が宿主を助けるはずだったときです
Then for example in the case of inflammation in the case of infection
次に、たとえば炎症の場合、感染症の場合
but it's a little too much
でもそれはちょっと多すぎる
So the result it gets is a problem for the human body
つまり、その結果は人体にとって問題となるのです
On the contrary, there is a great threat
逆に大きな脅威がある
that's what i think you should remember
それはあなたが覚えておくべきだと思うことです
10 years ago 10 years ago
10年前 10年前
SARS affected us a lot
SARSは私たちに大きな影響を与えました
2002 to 2003
2002年から2003年
In Asia, there are probably tens of thousands of this
アジアにはおそらく何万台もあるでしょう
People are affected
人々は影響を受ける
The number of people with 100,000 is also nearly 1,000
10万の人も1000人近くいる
The damage to the economy is about 40 billion US dollars.
経済へのダメージは約400億ドルに上る。
This is a
これは
When I found this effect
もともとこの効果を発見した
What caused SARS was a virus
SARSの原因はウイルスだった
Its name is the filling virus
その名は充填ウイルス
Because you can see this under a microscope
顕微鏡で見るとわかるので
Some prominent structures like Huangguan Zhouyuan
黄関周源などの著名な建造物
That's why it's called a filling virus
それが充填ウイルスと呼ばれる理由です
Then this was the serious infection caused by Taiwan
これが台湾による深刻な感染症だった
Many hospitals closed their eyes
多くの病院が目を閉じた
many people wearing masks
マスクをしている人が多い
Then this is the sanitation of front and rear recognition
それでは前後認識の衛生化です
The chief goes to the Peace Hospital
院長は平和病院へ
they dress inclusive
彼らは包括的な服装をします
Airtight clothes to the hospital to see
密閉性のある服を着て病院へ行ってください
This is the original case
これが元のケースです
About 600 to 700 people were affected
約600人から700人が被害を受けた
About 15% should be dead
15%くらいは死んでるはず
So everyone should have
だから誰もが持っているはずです
The number of frontlines is unknown
前線の数は不明
But there are about 300 deaths
でも死者は300人くらい
same as marching flu
行進インフルエンザと同じ
just have a fever and dizziness
ただ熱とめまいがある
temper oxygen headache
酸素による頭痛を和らげる
muscular mature
筋肉質の成熟した
throat cough etc.
喉の咳など
But it's most important
しかし、それが最も重要です
After it is infected by the virus
ウイルスに感染してからは
it affects the lungs
肺に影響を与える
then pneumonia
その後肺炎
when taking x-rays
X線写真を撮るとき
It doesn't look like the pneumonia is very serious
肺炎はそれほど深刻ではないようです
Some patients need a respirator to help keep him alive
命を保つために人工呼吸器が必要な患者もいる
Then about 10 to 15% of the cases are infected and he will not survive
その場合、感染者の約 10 ～ 15% が感染し、生存できなくなります。
Then this is the inflammatory response of the human body to the infection of this virus
これは、このウイルスの感染に対する人体の炎症反応です。
And this inflammatory response is too strong
そしてこの炎症反応は強すぎる
Therefore, it is called Sidokan stone at this time
そのため現在では紫道灌石と呼ばれています。
It's a storm of cytokines
サイトカインの嵐だ
I just mentioned cytokines and this Hemokan
先ほどサイトカインとこのヘモカンについて触れました。
is very important and plays an important role in the inflammatory response
非常に重要であり、炎症反応において重要な役割を果たします
But if he says it's too much
でも彼がそれはやりすぎだと言うなら
It is called Sidokan stone
シドカン石といいます
In this case
この場合
This is Sidokan's exaggerated immune response
これはシドカンの過剰な免疫反応です
or an inflammatory response that destroys tissue in the lungs
または肺の組織を破壊する炎症反応
The result was severe pneumonia.
結果は重度の肺炎でした。
In the following words, we will talk about inflammation, infection and wound repair
次の言葉では、炎症、感染、傷の修復について説明します。
Saying that he should be indispensable to this
それには彼が欠かせないはずだと言う
But in a way, he was supposed to be helpful against the hospital
しかしある意味、彼は病院に対して役立つはずだった
But if he goes too far, it will affect life and be dangerous
でも行き過ぎると生命に影響が出て危険です
I will now give a few other examples
他の例をいくつか紹介します
So it turns out, they're talking about acute inflammatory reactions
つまり、彼らは急性炎症反応について話していることがわかりました
Now let's talk about the chronic inflammatory response
さて、慢性炎症反応について話しましょう
Some things we've probably known from the past are inflammatory reactions.
私たちがおそらく過去から知っているいくつかのことは、炎症反応です。
But I will talk about a few more examples later because I didn’t know about it in the past.
しかし、私は過去にそれについて知らなかったので、後でさらにいくつかの例について説明します。
It is said that it is really caused by an inflammatory reaction.
実は炎症反応が原因と言われています。
It is now known that the inflammatory response plays an important role
炎症反応が重要な役割を果たしていることが現在では知られています
The first is the name
まずは名前です
I think what I said earlier was about cell bacterial infection
先ほど私が言ったのは細胞細菌感染症についてだったと思います
Then I think everyone in each district has experience with wounds
それから、各地域の誰もが傷を負った経験があると思います
If you are allergic, I think it is about ten or twenty percent.
アレルギーがある場合は10％か20％くらいだと思います。
So there will be allergies
だからアレルギーも出てくるんだよ
So there are probably a lot of faces when you are doing it.
なので、かなりの数の顔があるかもしれません
is aware of the effects of allergies
アレルギーの影響を知っている
this is an allergic reaction
これはアレルギー反応です
Then it usually means that there are some substances around us
その場合、それは通常、私たちの周りにいくつかの物質があることを意味します
should be humilus
屈辱的であるべきだ
But our bodies still respond
しかし、私たちの体はまだ反応しています
because it is forend
フォアエンドだから
But sometimes the reaction doesn't matter much
でも、反応があまり重要でない場合もあります
But for this kind of humilus
しかし、この種の屈辱に対して
it produces this reaction
それはこの反応を引き起こします
and the result of the reaction is an allergic reaction
そしてその反応の結果がアレルギー反応です
This substance we have to take care of is called allergy
私たちが注意しなければならないこの物質はアレルギーと呼ばれます
That's like skin contact
それはスキンコンタクトのようなものです
It’s Lujiao’s Latex
ルージャオのラテックスです
or animal hair
または動物の毛
Allergic skin reaction after contact with skin
皮膚との接触後のアレルギー皮膚反応
Some medicines in milk and milk can cause allergies
牛乳や牛乳に含まれる一部の薬はアレルギーを引き起こす可能性があります
Some of those are just that, for example, peanuts
それらの中には、たとえばピーナッツなどがあります。
caused by other lotuses
他の蓮が原因
Also very commonly seen by allergists
アレルギー専門医にもよく見られます
I heard recently that it is, for example, a child recently
最近聞いたのですが、例えば最近子供です。
This kind of allergy to this peanut is more and more
このピーナッツに対するこの種のアレルギーはますます増えています
It seems that it may be, for example, an inside
それは例えば内部である可能性があるようです
one in five
5人に1人
In fact, this allergy is getting more and more
実はこのアレルギーはますます増えています
The reason for that is wait a minute we have a chance
その理由は、ちょっと待ってください、チャンスはあるからです
Maybe talk a little more about why we have more and more allergies
なぜアレルギーが増えているのかについて、もう少し話してもいいかもしれません
that anyway
それはともかく
This is what causes allergies when you eat it
これを食べるとアレルギーが起きるのです
Sometimes by injection, medicine or honey
時には薬や蜂蜜
The venom of the honey bee ran into the human body
ミツバチの毒が人体に流れ込んだ
some people will be reborn
生まれ変わる人もいるだろう
allergic reaction
アレルギー反応
In addition, western words such as pollen
また、花粉などの西洋語も
i think some of you guys
皆さんの中にも何人かいると思います
Some of you will know from experience with hay fever
花粉症の経験がある方もいらっしゃると思いますが、
black pneumonia
黒色肺炎
That's because there are some proteins in the pollen
花粉にはたんぱく質が含まれているからです
to it will produce
それが生み出すだろう
It is some substance that should be homeless
それはホームレスになるべき物質です
But after you inhale
でも吸い込んだ後は
had this allergic reaction
このアレルギー反応がありました
If the dust is not the dust itself
塵が塵そのものでないなら
It's the mite inside the dust, which is full of dust
ホコリだらけのホコリの中にいるダニです
also an allergy
アレルギーでもある
that plum fungus, that has hair
あの梅菌には毛がある
What about those allergies?
それらのアレルギーについてはどうですか？
usually begins in childhood
通常は幼少期に始まります
There are several different ways of expressing these
これらを表現するにはいくつかの異なる方法があります
One is private, that is skin
1つはプライベート、それは肌です
odorous dermatitis
臭い皮膚炎
That's usually odorous dermatitis first.
通常、最初は臭気性皮膚炎です。
Then, at the same time
それから同時に
In childhood, for example, at about six months, it can occur at about one to two years old, and the incidence rate is relatively high.
小児では、例えば生後6か月頃から1～2歳頃に発症することもあり、発生率は比較的高いです。
15 Over rice is another, also a kind of allergies
15 ご飯食べ過ぎもアレルギーの一種
Then there will be wheezing, and finally rhinitis will come out
その後喘鳴が起こり、最後には鼻炎が出てきます。
This order is not necessarily like this, but most of them are like this, so this is called allergic march
この順番が必ずこうなるというわけではありませんが、ほとんどがこのようになるので、これをアレルギーマーチと呼びます。
These are all related to an allergic disease
これらはアレルギー疾患に関連しています
Fortunately, if you are allergic at 15, it usually disappears after a few years
幸いなことに、15 歳でアレルギーがある場合、通常は数年後には消えます。
This treatment will also gradually improve, and the same is true for breathlessness.
この治療により徐々に改善していきますが、息切れも同様です。
Rhinitis will be easier to continue until adulthood
大人になるまで鼻炎が続きやすい
Of course, these all start when you are an adult, and there are also such
もちろん、これらはすべて大人になってから始まります。
Let's talk about allergic reactions
アレルギー反応について話しましょう
just mentioned
先ほど述べた
B is 08 cells, two of them are T and B
B は 08 セルで、そのうちの 2 つは T と B
Let's talk about B cells first
まずはB細胞について話しましょう
B cells produce antibodies
B細胞は抗体を産生します
For example, IGM, IGG, the most IGG, IGA
例: IGM、IGG、最も IGG、IGA
In addition, the least is IGE
また、最も少ないのは IGE です
This IGE produced an over-reaction, the most important role
このIGEは過剰反応を引き起こし、最も重要な役割を果たしました
IGE antibody
IGE抗体
IGE has a special feature, it is another cell
IGEには特別な機能があり、それは別の細胞です
It's related to allergic reactions, yes, it's related to anti-antireactions.
それはアレルギー反応に関連しています、そうです、それは抗抗反応に関連しています。
And it's very related to allergic reactions, called mast cells
そして、それはマスト細胞と呼ばれるアレルギー反応に非常に関係しています
That's called MASO
それはMASOと呼ばれます
IGE will have its receptors on this
IGE はこれに受容体を置きます
so it attaches to the mast cells
肥満細胞に付着するので、
If this is true, it is wrong, it should be the other way around
これが本当なら、それは間違いで、その逆であるべきです
reverse like this
このように逆にします
It is anti-inflammatory and allergic
抗炎症作用とアレルギー作用がある
Connect to this MASTER
このマスターに接続します
Then the allergic person in
それからアレルギーの人は
these are allergies
これらはアレルギーです
allergic person
過敏人
Then when you see someone with allergies
そして、アレルギーのある人を見ると、
He will activate this MASTER
彼はこのマスターを起動します
MASTER will generate
MASTERが生成します
like organizing MMA
MMAを組織するような
There are other substances that can be called sensitive
他にも敏感と言える物質はあります
I think everyone has heard of this HISTOMINE
誰もがこのヒストミンについて聞いたことがあると思います
would be called, say, WT runny nose
たとえば、WT 鼻水と呼ばれるでしょう
just shed tears
ただ涙を流した
or red eyes
または赤い目
These phenomena
こういった現象は
that's sensitive
それは敏感です
It's a sensitive reaction
敏感な反応です
THAT HISTOMINE IS IMPORTANT
ヒストミンが重要であること
important cause of sensitivity
知覚過敏の重要な原因
that's a little bit deeper
それはもう少し深いです
It is how the BBC bag is made to cause IGE
IGEを引き起こすBBCバッグの作り方
Because it is the control of T cells
T細胞のコントロールだから
So T cells are more commanding
したがって、T細胞はより秩序立っています
this cell
この細胞
It will talk to the BBC package
BBCパッケージと通信します
You have to develop antibodies
抗体を開発する必要がある
And I first T cells will talk to the BBC package
そして私は最初に T 細胞が BBC パッケージと会話します
You have to create antibodies that are IGE
IGEである抗体を作成する必要があります
How do T cells know that there are these fermenter forces?
T細胞はどのようにしてこれらの発酵力が存在することを知るのでしょうか?
Another very important cell, this should probably be Commander
もう 1 つの非常に重要なセル、これはおそらく司令官であるはずです
It is called looking at the source and presenting cells, that is, Energy Preserving Cells
それは、ソースを見て細胞を提示する、つまりエネルギー保存細胞と呼ばれます。
The other name is Dendry Cell, which is called polar cells
別名はデンドリーセル、極細胞とも呼ばれます。
The reason for the polar shape is because it is born like a touch shake, called Dendry Cell
極の形状の理由は、デンドリーセルと呼ばれるタッチシェイクのように生まれるからです
This is a very important cell
とても大切な細胞です
Talking about a gap is last year's Nobel Prize
ギャップについて語るのが昨年のノーベル賞
Given to Ross Diamond of Immunology at Rockupill University
ロックピル大学免疫学のロス・ダイアモンド氏に贈呈
It is because it discovered Dendry Cell, so it holds the Nobel Prize
デンドリー細胞を発見したからノーベル賞
But sadly, it's also fun
でも悲しいけど楽しいことでもある
It was actually three days before the price was announced, it was too much
価格が発表されるのは実際には3日前でした、あまりにも多すぎました
Then this inner guard card is usually not given to the deceased.
そして、この内なるガードカードは通常、故人には渡されません。
It's not the one who lives now that will be given again
再び与えられるのは今生きている人ではない
when we were inside
私たちが中にいたとき
Because everyone knows that he is not in good health
なぜなら、彼の健康状態が良くないことは誰もが知っているからです。
In fact he is a handicapped cancer
実は彼は障害者ガンです
But the committee member of the inner guard
でも内衛委員は
he is not sure
他不太確定
don't know his illness
彼の病気を知りません
His hands are already ashamed
彼の手はすでに恥ずかしいです
that close
それは近い
Didn't know he was dead when it was announced
死亡が発表されたときは知らなかった
But he finally decided to give him
しかし、彼は最終的に彼に与えることに決めました
Give this award to his kid guest
この賞をゲストのお子様に贈ります
Although his contribution is very large
彼の貢献は非常に大きいですが、
Also because he studies this
また、彼はこれを勉強しているので、
This is a very important cell
とても大切な細胞です
I just said he gave orders
彼が命令したと言ったところだ
So it is very important in the immune response
したがって、免疫反応において非常に重要です
doing that now
今それをやってる
character award like this
キャラクター賞はこんな感じ
like cancer
癌のように
but i won't say a word
でも私は何も言いません
cancer treatments
がん治療
One way is to
1つの方法は、
See how we can use our immune system
私たちの免疫システムをどのように活用できるかを見てみましょう
look at cancer
がんを見てください
that it because
それはだから
But this becomes a very important type of cell
しかし、これは非常に重要な種類の細胞になります
Then it's because of research on this
それはこれについての研究によるものです
So it uses its own cell
したがって、独自のセルを使用します
to treat my pancreatic cancer
膵臓がんを治療するために
Turns out it actually works for it
実際に効果があることが判明
So it only gets after pancreatic cancer
つまり、膵臓がんの後にのみ発生します
it survived for about five or six years
5、6年くらい生き続けた
five or six years
5、6年
just passed away
亡くなったばかりです
If it doesn't have this
これがなかったら
i don't think it can get it
それは手に入らないと思います
nobel prize
ノーベル賞
Because the Nobel Prize is
なぜならノーベル賞は、
always have to wait a few years
いつも何年も待ちます
after knowing its fruit
その実を知ってから
to give it
それを与える
But it is a pity that in
しかし、残念なことに、
three days before the announcement
発表の3日前に
it passed away
それは過ぎ去った
it doesn't know itself
それ自体を知りません
so it got the nobel prize
それでノーベル賞を取った
That's almost
それはほぼ
OK, that's strictly normal
OK、それはまったく普通のことです
it this is a
それは
also a cartoon
漫画も
it's an allergic reaction
それはアレルギー反応です
mast cells
肥満細胞
it's a mast cell
それはマスト細胞です
This is sealed venom, entering this is a Myself
これは封印された毒 これに入るのは私自身
And there's a lot of Grammy that produces Histamine
そして、ヒスタミンを生成するグラミー賞がたくさんあります
There's particles over here, this is IgE, this is allergen
ここに粒子があります、これは IgE、これはアレルゲンです
After receiving its signal, it will enter
信号を受信した後、侵入します
Then these particles with Histamine will be expelled
その後、ヒスタミンを含むこれらの粒子は排出されます
that is an allergic reaction
それはアレルギー反応です
That is the Histamine tissue plant
それがヒスタミン組織植物です
But the cartoon is not actually right either
しかし、漫画も実際には正しくありません
So sometimes you're being a tribute at Google and it's not always completely
つまり、Google に敬意を表していることもありますが、必ずしも完全に敬意を表しているわけではありません。
is completely convinced that this is true
これが真実であると完全に確信している
Because of its Histamine release
ヒスタミンが放出されるため、
The cell is alive, it just takes its Histamine out
細胞は生きていて、ヒスタミンを取り出すだけです
But the cells still survive
しかし細胞はまだ生きています
But the change is as if the whole cell becomes scattered
でもその変化はまるで細胞全体が散らばるようだ
This is actually not true
これは実際には真実ではありません
It's related to allergies, it's related to B yuan, it's asthma
それはアレルギーに関係しています、それはB元に関係しています、それは喘息です
Asthma is more serious than
喘息はもっと深刻です
because it is sometimes hard to breathe
時々呼吸困難になることがあるので
This is what it looks like when the trachea is normal
気管が正常な場合は次のようになります
This is the trachea
これが気管です
This is the respiratory tract
ここは気道です
when panting
あえぐとき
One is why you are short of breath
息切れする理由の1つは
A big reason is that it has Bronco Contrusion
大きな理由はブロンココントラクションを搭載していることです。
it's muscle tension
それは筋肉の緊張です
So its trachea constricts
それで気管が収縮する
Once it shrinks, it passes through and becomes much smaller
一度縮むと突き抜けてさらに小さくなる
so it's hard to breathe
だから呼吸が難しい
so the cause of asthma
だから喘息の原因は
But this is in the past, for example, more than 30 years
しかし、これは過去の話、たとえば 30 年以上前のことです。
when it comes to breathlessness
息切れに関しては
Everyone said this is the reason
みんなこれが理由だと言ってた
but now we know
しかし今私たちは知っています
In fact, it is such an important role as Information
実際、それは情報として非常に重要な役割です
Information For example, the production of its mucus
情報 たとえば、粘液の生成
also cause difficulty breathing
呼吸困難も引き起こす
also because of the inflammatory response
炎症反応のせいでもある
In addition is
さらに、
maybe not easy to imagine
想像するのは簡単ではないかもしれません
but in the process
しかしその過程で
In fact, it is equivalent to having injury in this part
実はこの部分に怪我をしているのと同じです
I just said that inflammation is trauma, internal injury
炎症は外傷、内部損傷だと言いました
This can also be thought of as a kind of internal injury.
これも一種の内部損傷と考えることができます。
This internal injury is actually caused by an inflammatory response.
この内部損傷は実際には炎症反応によって引き起こされます。
So which is the cause and which is the effect
では、どちらが原因でどちらが結果なのか
it is hard to distinguish
区別するのは難しい
but what if
でももし
Here's what caused it in the first place
そもそもの原因はこれだ
not sure
わからない
But with this inflammation
しかし、この炎症では
after inflammation
炎症の後
It's going to be kind of hurt over here
ここはちょっと痛いことになるだろう
Repay after injury
怪我後の返済
But it keeps hurting and repaying
でも傷つき続けて報われていく
The final result is that the lining on this side is getting thicker and thicker.
最終的な結果は、こちら側の裏地がどんどん厚くなっていくということです。
The thicker the pain the less
厚みがあればあるほど痛みは少なくなります
Plus it's smaller after muscle tension
さらに、筋肉の緊張後は小さくなります
So it's hard to breathe at this time
だから最後は息が苦しくなる
So it is also a relationship between inflammation and disease
つまり、炎症と病気の関係でもあります
words here
ここの言葉
I didn't know why these patients had some inflammatory reactions
なぜこれらの患者が炎症反応を起こしたのかわかりませんでした
But in the end the inflammatory response is what affects the disease
しかし、最終的に病気に影響を与えるのは炎症反応です
And let this disease to the end and even to the extent of life
そしてこの病気が死ぬまで続くように
That inflammatory response plays a big role
その炎症反応が大きな役割を果たしている
good
良い
So what about national treatment and prevention?
それでは、内国民待遇と予防についてはどうなるのでしょうか？
In this raw material, what I want to talk about is
この原材料で話したいのは、
We learn more and more about the inflammatory response
炎症反応についてはさらに詳しくわかっています
The development of science is really long-term
科学の発展は本当に長期にわたるものです
Maybe you won't see it in the short term
もしかしたら短期間では見えなくなるかもしれない
But like this allergic reaction
でも、このアレルギー反応のように
I used to know that there was such a reaction
そういう反応があるのは知ってた
Gradually know what kind of cell I am
自分がどんな細胞なのかだんだんわかってくる
For example, mast cells
たとえば、マスト細胞
What about this progress?
この進歩についてはどうですか？
will let us know how to treat
治療方法を教えてください
And here is a good example
そして、これが良い例です
so it's farther away after
だからその後はさらに遠くなる
Our treatment methods are getting better and better
私たちの治療方法はどんどん良くなっていきます
that's just generally speaking
それは一般的に言っていることです
we want a cure
私たちは治療法が欲しいのです
One is to avoid allergens
一つはアレルゲンを避けること
Of course, if there are no allergens
もちろんアレルゲンがなければ
not sensitive
敏感ではない
but it's hard to do
でもそれは難しい
then follow some statement
その後、何らかのステートメントに従ってください
It depends on the organization
それは組織によります
For example, I want this
たとえば、これが欲しいです
I think you have some
いくつか持っていると思います
Maybe use this too
これも使ってみようかな
to sustain this statement
この声明を支持するために
sensitive reaction
敏感な反応
That kind of estimation is very effective
このような推定は非常に効果的です
it has many side effects
多くの副作用があります
The method of desensitization
減感作の方法
just if you know it's
それがわかっていれば
sensitive to what
何に対して敏感か
is sensitive
敏感です
You can use the doctor will take allergens
医師がアレルゲンを摂取することができます
very small doses
非常に少量の投与量
inject it
それを注入する
Then slowly increase the dose
その後徐々に投与量を増やしていきます
and after a while
そしてしばらくしてから
this body
この体
know exactly why
正確に理由を知っています
The amount of IgE is getting less and less
IgEの量がどんどん減っていく
That's why you're allergic to this one
だからあなたはこれにアレルギーがあるのです
less and less
ますます少なくなる
so this is one way
これは一方的な方法です
this very old way
この非常に古い方法
but still continue to use
しかし、まだ使い続けています
But what I want to say most is
でも、一番言いたいのは、
Antibodies against IGE
IGEに対する抗体
this latest
この最新の
is a recent development
最近の発展です
Then this Professor Zhang Ziwen
それからこの張子文教授
He is also on this
彼もこれに参加しています
His company at the time, Tennox
当時の彼の会社、テノックス
Later, I cooperated with Ginetic two
その後、ジネティックツーと協力しました
developed this
これを開発した
called Omalizma
オマリズマと呼ばれる
or one of his
または彼の誰かの
Also called Zoleia
ゾレイアとも呼ばれる
But these antibodies
しかし、これらの抗体は
He can
彼はできる
just to see the IGE
IGEを見るためだけに
And let the IGE let the IGE
そして IGE には IGE を任せましょう
won't be able to have his activity anymore
もう彼の活動はできなくなるだろう
So draw it here
だからここに描いてください
This is IGE
これはIGEです
Then this Anti
じゃあこのアンチは
Antibodies against IGE
IGEに対する抗体
So both of them are antibodies
つまり両方とも抗体です
One is IGE
1つはIGEです
One is an antibody against IGE
1つはIGEに対する抗体です
So this IGE
それでこのIGE
was supposed to be responsible for the mast cell
肥満細胞を担当すると考えられていた
and then finally make this
そして最後にこれを作ります
mast cell activation
マスト細胞の活性化
Then the organization comforted and ran out
それから組織は慰めて逃げ出した
but now he won't let him
でも今は彼が許してくれない
This is passed by the Department of Health in the United States to let him treat this Qishuang
このQishuangを治療させるために、これが米国保健省によって認可されました。
In addition, it must be effective for rhinitis
また、鼻炎にも効果があるはずです
rhinitis is relatively
鼻炎は比較的
Rhinitis may not be completely IgE
鼻炎は完全にIgEではない可能性があります
So his main effect may not be useful to everyone
したがって、彼の主な効果は誰にとっても役立つわけではないかもしれません
But it should be useful for rhinitis
でも鼻炎には効くはず
Just say if you need to use this
これを使用する必要があるかどうかを言ってください
Because he has a lot of sense of safety from organization N, Histamine can use it
N組織の安心感が大きいのでヒスタミンが使える
Also he has food allergies which should help too
さらに、彼は食物アレルギーを持っているので、それも役立つはずです。
Another example we are talking about is Solitis
私たちが話している別の例はソリティスです
It's also a skin disease
これも皮膚病です
Also because I'm a dermatologist
皮膚科専門医なので
So I would like an example of a couple of skins
そこで、いくつかのスキンの例を追加したいと思います。
I think 10% to 20% of people have the sensitivity just mentioned
10％から20％の人が今述べた過敏症を持っていると思います
Less for Solitis
孤炎の場合は少ない
In Europe and the United States, it is 2%-3% of the population
ヨーロッパやアメリカでは人口の2%～3%
will be dangerous
危険になるだろう
For Taiwan, this number is 0.2%
台湾の場合、この数字は 0.2%
I think it's a little on the low side
少し低いほうだと思います
i think it should be
そうあるべきだと思う
if it's that low
そんなに低いなら
should have gone
行くべきだった
maybe an epidemic
もしかしたら流行病かもしれない
Experts should just look at
専門家はただ見てください
Do you know why it is so low
なぜこんなに低いか知っていますか
but i think it should be
でもそうあるべきだと思う
about the same
ほぼ同じ
So this figure is not reliable
したがって、この数字は信頼できません
so probably
だからおそらく
I think it is
それはそうですね
words from all over the world
世界中からの言葉
About 2%-3%
2%～3%程度
This is a recurrent chronic dermatitis
繰り返す慢性皮膚炎です
recurrent in fact
実際に再発する
it is in fact
それは実際にあります
If there is such a risk
そんなリスクがあるなら
is a lifetime
一生です
but it's better sometimes
でも時々その方が良いこともある
especially if you heal
特に治るなら
but even if
しかし、たとえ
After getting better
良くなってから
it will also be in
それも入ります
one for treatment and one for medicine
1つは治療用、もう1つは薬用
it will recur
それは再発します
but it's not contagious
しかしそれは伝染性ではありません
the skin will thicken
皮膚が厚くなる
Then there is the thick cuticle
それから厚いキューティクルがあります
vicious door bubble
悪質なドアバブル
Another name is medical disease
別の名前は医学的な病気です
on this epidermis
この表皮に
Needle skin has more capillaries
針の皮膚には毛細血管が多い
then inflammatory cells
次に炎症細胞
can be seen inside
中が見える
So it's an inflammatory response
つまり炎症反応です
a skin disease
皮膚病
The skin of the whole body will be affected
全身の皮膚に影響が出る
For example, the skin includes buttocks, nails
例えば、皮膚にはお尻や爪などが含まれます。
more importantly
さらに重要なことには
We now know it's not just the skin that's affected
影響を受けるのは皮膚だけではないことがわかっています
It's a Metabolic syndrome
メタボリックシンドロームだよ
it's blood generation syndrome
それは造血症候群です
So we need to pay attention to these patients
したがって、私たちはこれらの患者に注意を払う必要があります
heart problem is it diabetes
心臓の問題、それは糖尿病ですか
Usually they are a bit fatter
通常はもう少し太ります
so it is
それはそうです
What we now know about this inflammation
この炎症について現在わかっていること
It's also related to inflammation
炎症も関係してるよ
Although skin inflammation
皮膚に炎症があるのに、
but it affects the whole body
しかしそれは体全体に影響を与えます
So now there's a fluke
それで今はまぐれがいる
There is a name called blood generation syndrome
造血症候群という名前があります
the patient
その患者
Under this example
この例では
It affects 80% of the skin
皮膚の80％に影響を及ぼします
very serious
非常に深刻な
Look at this in recent years
近年のこれを見てください
This is what it shows
これがそれを示しています
this is the slice
これがスライスです
Microscope to see
見るための顕微鏡
Normal skin probably slightly
普通肌はおそらくわずかに
at most this thick
せいぜいこのくらいの厚さ
this word
この単語
Much thicker than normal skin
普通の皮膚よりもはるかに厚い
Here are the ones with inflammatory reactions
炎症反応を伴うものはこちら
responding cells
応答する細胞
if dyeing
染めるなら
you can see the cells that are inflamed
炎症を起こしている細胞が見える
these are here
これらはここにあります
quite severe inflammatory reaction
かなり重度の炎症反応
then cause the skin cells
そして皮膚細胞を引き起こす
multiply and become thicker
増えて太くなる
This is probably the most complicated one in my original house.
おそらくこれが私の元の家で最も複雑なものです。
So what I said earlier
それで、先ほど言ったことは
reduce it a bit
少し減らす
That is, what is the reaction to Mingchang?
つまり、ミンチャンに対する反応は何ですか？
here
ここ
let's talk a little bit more
もう少し話しましょう
because i want
私が欲しいから
You probably know a little bit more about it just now
おそらく今ならもう少し詳しくわかると思います
Each page responds to the manufacture of B cells and T cells
各ページはB細胞とT細胞の製造に対応します
So we're a little bit under Adventure
ということで、ちょっと冒険中です
The ones below this one won't be reclaimed anymore
これより下のものはもう回収されません
Another thing is
もう一つのことは、
here is a good story
ここに良い話があります
is the development of our treatment of tinea liver
肝臓白癬の治療法の開発です
It's true, it's our scientific development
それは本当です、それは私たちの科学の発展です
a good example
良い例
help with this disease
この病気を助けてください
So the words of the hand cancer doctor
そこで手のがんの医師の言葉
It also starts with external stimuli
それも外部からの刺激から始まります
There will be internal injuries after stimulation
刺激後は内部損傷が発生します
It’s not necessarily obvious what kind of stimulation it is
それがどのような刺激であるかは必ずしも明らかではありません
but always hurt
でもいつも傷つく
That is, the cells in the dermis will be injured
つまり、真皮の細胞が傷ついてしまうのです。
or some infection
または何らかの感染症
Finally, the extremely strong cells will activate
最後に非常に強力な細胞が活性化します
this is what i just said
これは私が今言ったことです
He's the whole guy who stays on the 18th
彼は18日に残る男だ
equal to oneself
自分と等しい
This is equal to itself, it will secrete
これはそれ自体に等しいので、分泌します
For example, this is cytokine
例えばこれはサイトカインです
Cytokines
サイトカイン
In fact there are dozens of
実際には数十個あります
I just said
私はちょうど言いました
Sarcolemmal Liver Cheek Liver
筋鞘肝臓 頬肝臓
This is the cheek liver
これが頬の肝臓です
now in fact there is
今、実際にあります
There are about 30 known cheek livers
頬の肝臓は約30個知られている
Immunology
免疫学
getting richer
より豊かになる
Cells are not just cells
細胞はただの細胞ではない
Kick cells come in a variety of
キックセルにはさまざまな種類があります
I won't talk about it today
今日はそれについては話しません
Cheek Liver, Cheek Liver as well
頬の肝臓、頬の肝臓も
not just one or two
1つや2つだけではなく
Instead, there are dozens of
その代わりに数十個あります
but for this
しかし、これに関しては
love is understanding
愛は理解することです
we just say yes
私たちはただ「はい」と言うだけです
Focus at I-12 I-23
I-12 I-23 に焦点を当てる
These cause the proliferation of kick cells
これらはキック細胞の増殖を引き起こします
this kick cell
このキックセル
and then secrete
そして分泌する
other cytokines
他のサイトカイン
It's called Interferon Gamma
インターフェロンガンマといいます
or TNF Alpha
またはTNFアルファ
These will have two different effects
これらには 2 つの異なる効果があります
One is inside the tissue cells
1つは組織細胞内にあります
Let the surrounding tissue cells secrete some other substances
周囲の組織細胞に他の物質を分泌させる
or let the tissue cells proliferate
または組織細胞を増殖させます
That's why the epidermis on the cell side becomes thicker.
そのため細胞側の表皮が厚くなるのです。
It also makes the blood vessels respond
血管も反応します
And the first cartoon is when the germs come in
そして最初の漫画は細菌が入ってきたときです
Vascular reaction, the white blood cells will come out
血管反応、白血球が出てきます
the same here
こっちも一緒
Because these cells produced by this T cell
なぜなら、これらの細胞はこのT細胞によって作られるからです。
It's low speed, it will stimulate the blood vessels
低速なので血管を刺激します
The mononuclear spheres inside will come out.
中の単核球が出てきます。
Then the mononuclear sphere still has the original myocytes
その後、単核球には元の筋細胞がまだ残っています
They also produce TNFF like this one
彼らはまた、このようなTNFFを生成します
It also causes the secretion and proliferation of pericytes
また、周皮細胞の分泌と増殖も引き起こします。
Then here the dry display is generated
次に、ここでドライ表示が生成されます
So this is a dry and pathogenic muscle transfer
つまり、これは乾燥した病原性の筋肉転移です
That's what has been studied over the years.
それが何年にもわたって研究されてきたことです。
Do step by step turn this into this
これを段階的にこれに変えてください
As the mechanism of the
その仕組みとしては、
Let me talk about this a little bit more
これについてもう少しお話しましょう
is a disease
病気です
that's why this stimulus
だからこそこの刺激は
clinically
臨床的に
is there some kind of phenomenon
何か現象があるのでしょうか
That is, if hand cancer is almost cured
つまり、手がんがほぼ治癒した場合
Or you just have some skin diseases
それともただ皮膚病を患っているだけですか
part of it doesn't
一部はそうではありません
But if you get hurt over there
でもそこで怪我をしたら
That part will still come out at that time
その部分はその時にまだ出てくるでしょう
Hepatic glands are also shown
肝腺も表示されています
So say this is right
だからこれが正しいと言ってください
after stimulation
刺激以後
How to cause the activation here is not sure
ここでアクティベーションを引き起こす方法は不明です
But there is a way
しかし、方法はあります
let this show it's an irritation an injury
これはイライラ、怪我であることを示しましょう
that just said
それは今言ったばかりです
that liver gland is
その肝臓腺は
yes
はい
Cardiometabolic Neutralization Syndrome
心代謝中和症候群
So it's not just
だからそれだけではない
liver gland
肝腺
It's inflamed
炎症を起こしている
hepatic glandular arthritis
肝腺関節炎
Usually the hepatic glands start first
通常、肝腺が最初に始まります
say ten years later
10年後に言う
These arthritis will come out
これらの関節炎が出てきます
not everyone will
誰もがそうするわけではありません
For example, one hundred and twenty percent would
たとえば、120 パーセントは
have this arthritis
この関節炎がある
quite serious
かなり深刻な
that diabetes
その糖尿病
More patients with hepatic glands
肝腺疾患の患者が増加
then in the liver
それから肝臓で
People with hepatic glands usually
肝腺のある人は通常、
They are also more likely to see obesity
肥満になる可能性も高くなります
Then these are Metabolic syndrome
それならメタボリックシンドロームですよ
It's all about inflammation
すべては炎症に関するものです
direct or indirect relationship
直接的または間接的な関係
What about the treatment?
治療についてはどうですか？
the traditional treatment
伝統的な治療法
lots of lotion
たくさんのローション
salve for inner lips
唇の内側用の軟膏
you can imagine
これは想像できますね
If the whole body has it
全身にあると
it's going to be very difficult
とても難しいだろう
Apply this to this clean place
これをこのきれいな場所に塗ります
off line treatment
オフライン処理
This is usually done with UV light
これは通常、UVライトを使用して行われます
this is local
これは地元です
But it can also be done for the whole body
でも全身にもできますよ
the stomach medicine
胃の薬
It is Metroflexid
メトロフレキシドです
pretty strong medicine
かなり強い薬
But it has some side effects, such as the liver, not cause hepatitis
しかし、肝臓に肝炎を引き起こさないなど、いくつかの副作用があります。
The recent progress is like this, which advertises the treatment
最近の経過はこんな感じです、治療法を宣伝します
Just now I mentioned the method of TNF, TNF is Trumer Necrosis Factor
先ほどTNFの方法について触れましたが、TNFとはトルーマー壊死因子のことです。
here, here oh, here
ここ、ここ、ああ、ここ
I'll talk about TNF Alpha later when I talk about Trumer
TNF アルファについては、後でトルーマーについて話すときに話します。
very important cell technology
非常に重要な細胞技術
So these pharmaceutical companies want to say that since TNF Alpha can cause hepatitis to hepatitis
つまり、これらの製薬会社は、TNFαが肝炎を引き起こす可能性があると言いたいのです。
So should we also make this antibody to cover it
じゃあそれをカバーする抗体も作ろうかな
just make it inactive
非アクティブにするだけです
The IGE we just talked about has antibody antibodies, preventing IG from acting
先ほどお話しした IGE には抗体があり、IG の作用を妨げます。
Similarly, antibodies can also be made
同様に抗体も作ることができます
Don't let this TF Alpha work
このTFアルファを働かせないでください
So he can't do anything to affect the keratinocytes
したがって、彼はケラチノサイトに影響を与えるために何もすることができません
Then this is the first company made by Sentako
では、これがセンタコが作った最初の会社です
At this time, it was because of the antibodies produced in the mice
この時はマウスの体内で作られた抗体のせいでした。
So he later had part of the mouse protein
それで彼は後にマウスのタンパク質の一部を摂取しました
The other company is Ebbett
相手の会社はエベットです
He turned him into an antibody that is all Human
彼は彼を完全に人間の抗体に変えます
The other company belongs to MGN
他の会社はMGNに属します
He does it with his receptors
彼は受容体を使ってそれを行う
Because his receptors are supposed to surround TF Alpha
彼の受容体はTFアルファを取り囲んでいるはずだから
Don't let him say let him not work
彼に仕事をさせないでくれと言わせないでください
It can only work on cells
細胞にしか作用しない
But if he divides it out, it is not on the cell
でも彼がそれを分けても、それは独房には入らない
But when he took it out, he would wrap it up to prevent him from functioning.
しかし、彼はそれを取り出すと、機能しないようにそれを包みました。
So these are the drugs made by these three different pharmaceutical companies
これらは、これら 3 つの異なる製薬会社によって製造された薬です
Now patients with clean stomachs can use it
胃がきれいな患者でも使用できるようになりました
Then this is a pharmaceutical factory
じゃあここは製薬工場だ
Twice a week used to be like inserting medicine
週に2回は薬を入れるようなものでした
plug in every day
毎日プラグインする
That said, it's only been about three months
とは言え、まだ3ヶ月くらいしか経っていないのですが、
twice a week
週二回
But then once a week is fine
でもそれなら週に1回でもいいよ
That's every two weeks
じゃあこの言葉は2週間に1回
That was about two or three years ago
あれは2、3年くらい前の話
Another company made this one from Synical
別の会社がこれをSynicalによって製造しました
It acts on i12 and 23
i12 および 23 で動作します
then come back here
それからここに戻ってきてください
Here are the packed cells
こちらがパックされたセルです
It was first clearly 12 and 23
最初は明らかに12と23でした
and then cause these reactions in the later stage
そして後の段階でこれらの反応を引き起こします
Then what their company does is
では、彼らの会社がやっているのは、
just made antibodies
抗体を作ったばかりです
i12, i23 able to get lost
i12、i23は迷子になる可能性があります
Then this is the injection of the patient
それからこれは患者への注射です
Then call again in a month
それから1か月後にまた電話してください
Then every three months
それから3ヶ月ごとに
It becomes four times a year
年に4回になります
four times a year
一年直四次
I can fight myself
自分自身と戦うことができる
I just came out with one
たった一個だけ出てきたよ
very serious patient
非常に深刻な患者
After playing like this
こうやって遊んだ後は
he will stay for a while
彼はしばらく滞在するでしょう
he has almost nothing to love
彼には愛するものがほとんど何もない
so this is very big
これはとても大きいです
and make people feel
そして人々に感じさせる
There are some developments to be excited about
楽しみな展開がいくつかある
is our response to inflammation
炎症に対する私たちの反応です
The same goes for other diseases
他の病気でも同様です
after knowing more
もっと学んでから
Then our medicine will be better
そうすれば私たちの薬は良くなるでしょう
good
良い
Let's talk about the other two chronic inflammation
他の 2 つの慢性炎症について話しましょう
I don't know when
いつなのかわからない
Time Magazine above
上のタイム誌
Especially when it comes to Information
特に情報に関しては
Talk about being a Secret Killer
シークレットキラーであることについて話す
Just those psoriasis, sensitive
乾癬で敏感な人だけ
What we know is obviously that there is
私たちが知っているのは、明らかに存在するということです
Then know it's inflammation
それなら炎症だとわかる
but in some cases
しかし場合によっては
We don't know there is inflammation
炎症があるかどうかはわかりません
or unexpected inflammation
または予期せぬ炎症
be the cause of disease
病気の原因になる
It's serious in the end
結局深刻なんだよ
Here's what it says
これがその内容です
Suppressing link between inflammation and heart attacks and cancer and Alzheimer's
炎症と心臓発作、がんとアルツハイマー病との関連を抑制
Let me talk, I will talk about heart attack and cancer
話しましょう、心臓発作と癌について話します
Y'all know Alzheimer's is dementia
アルツハイマー病が認知症であることは皆さんご存知です
is a serious problem
深刻な問題です
In fact, we now also know that he is such an important role as Information
実際、私たちは彼が情報担当者として非常に重要な役割を果たしているということも知っています。
There is information in the brain of the patient
患者の脳には情報がある
And he ended up getting Alzheimer's symptoms
そして結局アルツハイマー病の症状が出てしまった
I saw a news yesterday
昨日ニュースを見ました
was published in the journal Nature Medicine
Nature Medicine誌に掲載されました
they had a team i no longer remember which school it was
彼らにはどの学校だったかもう覚えていないチームがありました
There's a mouse, they're Genetic Modified mice
マウスがいます、それは遺伝子組み換えマウスです
He started this automatically after their rat quarantine
彼はネズミの隔離後にこれを自動的に開始しました
don't use any way
いかなる方法も使用しないでください
He will automatically develop symptoms like Oscar
彼はオスカーのような症状を自動的に発症するでしょう
In addition, we know that Oskanme just said that it has something to do with the reaction to the speech
さらに、オスカンメ氏が演説への反応と関係があると述べたこともわかっています。
In fact, two important
実は、重要なことが 2 つあります
not rely on them
彼らに頼らないでください
But the important roles of these two battles are I-20, I-12, and I-23
しかし、この二つの戦いで重要な役割を担うのは伊-20、伊-12、伊-23です。
It's about SWICE
SWICEのことです
The team injected I-12, I-23 Anybody into this mouse
チームはこのマウスに I-12、I-23 を注入しました
like swice patients
スイスの患者のように
As a result, one month later the mice were initially injected
その結果、1か月後、マウスに最初の注射が行われました。
After a month his symptoms were reduced by 30, 30, 40%
1 か月後、彼の症状は 30、30、40% 軽減されました。
If there are some rats that already have symptoms, call him again
すでに症状が出ているネズミがいる場合は、もう一度電話してください
He will also reduce the symptoms of Oscammy
彼はオスカミーの症状も軽減します
So I believe this will be doing clinical trials soon
ですから、これはすぐに臨床試験が行われると思います
Because this medicine has been used for infection
この薬は感染症に使用されているため
So is it in Oscar now?
それで、今はオスカーにいますか？
it will also be useful, it will be helpful
これも役に立ちます、また役に立ちます
But we can actually expect to say whether there is
しかし、実際に存在するかどうかを言うことが期待できます。
Is it an advance in this regard?
この点に関しては進歩でしょうか？
So it is said that it can treat Alzheimer's
アルツハイマー病の治療に効果があると言われています
Of course, there will be other advances in the future.
もちろん、将来的には他の進歩もあるでしょう。
I just hope that after understanding this information
この情報を理解した上で、
able to have better medicines
より良い薬を手に入れることができる
Then Alzheimer will not talk about it
そうすればアルツハイマーはそれについて話さなくなる
Then talk about Heart Attack and Cancer
それから心臓発作とがんについて話します
So what I said earlier is what we usually see
先ほど言ったことは、比較から私が通常感じていることです
of the disease, all of you are experienced
この病気については、皆さんも経験があるでしょう
Then I will talk about it later, I hope everyone
それについては後ほどお話しますので、皆さんもよろしくお願いします
is not affected
影響を受けません
But this normal Colonial artery
しかし、この正常な植民地動脈
This coronary artery
この冠状動脈は
this young time
この若い頃
We want our coronary arteries to look like this too
私たちの冠動脈もこうであってほしい
But gradually there will be some cases
でも徐々にそういうケースも出てくるだろう
there will be some arteries on weekends
週末には動脈がいくつかあります
I'm in the past
私は過去にいる
In particular, the original lecture should be learned
オリジナルの講義は特に学ぶことが重要です
But it is good to keep Azure Scrooge
でもアズール・スクルージを残しておくのは良いことだ
Then you see its blood vessels become narrow
すると血管が狭くなるのがわかります
At this time, if there is Block Cloud
この時、ブロッククラウドがあれば
it doesn't work at all
まったく機能しません
At this time, because of the coronavirus, buying more is
現時点では、コロナウイルスの影響で、追加購入は困難です。
need blood transfusion
輸血が必要です
And Nutrition to the cells of the heart
そして心臓の細胞に栄養を与える
Therefore, if the blood vessels cannot be blocked
したがって、血管を遮断できない場合は、
These blood vessels will die
これらの血管は死んでしまいます
At the end is a Heart Attack
最後は心臓発作です
This definition is because
この定義は次の理由からです。
Substances of Fat and Cholesterol
脂肪とコレステロールの物質
Scores in vessel B which lead to vessel imprinting
血管インプリンティングにつながる血管 B のスコア
so it's normal
だからそれが普通です
And here's Azure Scrooge
そしてこちらがアズール・スクルージです
It's called a plaque and it seems to be
プラークと呼ばれるものらしいです
About 1000 people, there are about 7 people
1000人くらいで7人くらいですかね
But this is the whole population
しかし、これは全人口です
Of course it will be the most when you are older
もちろん大人になってからがそれが一番多くなります。
In the U.S. there are approximately 5 million
アメリカには約500万人いる
get this arteriosclerosis
この動脈硬化が起こる
What about the symptoms?
症状についてはどうでしょうか？
words in the heart
心の中の言葉
dear words
親愛なる言葉
there will be pain in the heart and feet
心臓と足に痛みが出るでしょう
words in that
その中の言葉
fatal myocardial infarction
致死性心筋梗塞
brain words
脳の言葉
Feel dizzy and headache when kissing
キスするとめまいや頭痛を感じる
when the face is heavy
顔が重いとき
there will be a stroke of haste
速攻が起こるだろう
When the blood vessels in the feet
足の血管が詰まると、
some
いくつかの
ischemic necrosis of lower extremities
下肢の虚血性壊死
that sometimes have to
時々そうしなければならないこと
congealing
結脂
then you can save your life
そうすればあなたの命を救うことができます
why?
なぜ？
the reason is
その理由は
of course
もちろん
the disease just mentioned
今言った病気
almost always some
ほとんどいつもある程度の
family death
家族病死
would be more stupid
もっと愚かだろう
This is no exception
これも例外ではありません
that time of aging
老化のその時
This heart is easier to harden
この心は固まりやすい
What's more, high blood pressure
しかも高血圧
also a big reason
それも大きな理由
the diabetic patient
糖尿病患者
easier to get
入手しやすい
Can be used until hardened
硬化するまで使用可能
external factors
外部要因
If it is a film and television with a bold process
大胆な加工を施した映画やテレビであれば
I think you should be very clear
はっきりと言うべきだと思います
Or smoking will harden this anime too
それとも喫煙するとこのアニメも硬くなるよ
The reason is what is its mechanism?
その理由はどのような仕組みになっているのでしょうか？
If collesterol is high
コレステロールが高い場合
especially low density
特に密度が低い
A wave of protein
一波protein
It will settle down in the school tube
学管に落ち着くだろう
it will be modified
変更されます
modify is actually oxidized
変更は実際には酸化されます
These oxidized LDA
これらの酸化されたLDAは、
will be eaten by megalithic cells or aggregated cells
巨石細胞や凝集した細胞に食べられる
These produce an inflammatory response
これらは炎症反応を引き起こします
The entire school tube has some inflammation around the week
週ごとに学管全体に炎症が起きている
And the final result is anime hardening
そして最終結果はアニメ硬化です
This is a beautiful cartoon
これは美しい漫画です
write slightly more clearly
もう少しはっきりと書きましょう
this is LDL it will come in
これはLDLです、入ってきます
Cholesterol
コレステロール
then it gets oxidized
そうすると酸化してしまう
how is it
どうですか
It will activate the B cells of this blood vessel
この血管のB細胞を活性化します
Then Molicyte will come in
そうするとモリサイトが入ってくる
After coming in, it will clear Modified LDL
入ってくるとModified LDLをクリアします
Oxidl LDL
オキシジルLDL
Then it ends up being all in
そうすると結局全部入ってしまいます
We are called Formcell
私たちはフォームセルと呼ばれています
This is also easier to activate
これも有効化が簡単です
And it secretes some substances that cause inflammation
そして炎症を引き起こす物質を分泌します
So here it becomes and these Colesterols are there
ここにコレステロールが存在します
another inflammatory reaction
別の炎症反応
This is blood going on here
ここでは血が流れている
this is a blood vessel
これは血管です
Here are blood vessels B
こちらが血管Bです
So the word here is the so-called plaque
つまり、ここでの言葉はいわゆるプラークです
At the same time, this inflammatory response will make the
同時に、この炎症反応により、
muscle cells proliferate
筋肉細胞が増殖する
Then it will bury and come to this place
そして埋もれてこの場所に来るだろう
So blood vessels are getting thicker and thicker
そのため、血管はどんどん太くなっていきます
less and less blood vessels
血管がどんどん減っていく
Getting smaller and smaller
どんどん小さくなっていきます
So it can be seen here
だからそれはここで見ることができます
That's where the plaque is created
そこでプラークが作られます
muscle cells here
ここの筋肉細胞
these are cells
これらは細胞です
You can see the words here
ここで言葉を見ることができます
here is getting thicker
ここは厚くなっています
But here the coins of the blood vessels of the cells
しかし、ここでは細胞の血管のコインが
is getting thinner
薄くなっています
If compared with the original
オリジナルと比べてみると
The port is getting smaller and smaller
通口越來越小
If there's an inflammatory reaction here, it's going to be a problem.
ここに炎症反応があれば大変なことになります。
that's what's causing this side
それがここにある理由です
will affect the injury here
ここの怪我に影響します
So many inflammatory reactions will be linked with injury
非常に多くの炎症反応が損傷に関連している
Here, in this case, when there is injury
ここで、この場合、怪我をしたときは、
It's like saying this is when we usually bleed
いつもは血が出る時期だと言っているようなものだ
it has solidified
固まりました
like i just said it was the one
さっき言ったように、それがその人だった
There will be bleeding when the wound will come in the school version
学校版では傷が入ると出血します
Of course it freezes, and it's the same here
もちろんフリーズします、それはここでも同じです
Here's the last thrombus
これが最後の血栓です
After a thrombus occurs, this side will not pass through.
血栓ができるとこちら側は通れなくなります。
Then this is what causes HotelTab
これが HotelTab の原因です
The same is for us to know and say yes
私たちが知って「はい」と言うのも同じです
This arteriosclerosis is related to inflammation
この動脈硬化は炎症に関係しています
So many companies began to study to see if inflammation
非常に多くの企業が炎症を確認するために研究を始めました
See if the inflammatory drug can treat this heart disease
炎症薬がこの心臓病を治療できるかどうかを確認する
Many of these children in the face to face tree
これらの子供たちの多くは向かい合って木にいます
Let me give you two examples
2つの例を挙げましょう
The first one is that this is anti-oxidation of LDA
1つ目は、これがLDAの抗酸化作用であるということです。
I just mentioned that LDA is oxidized first
LDA が最初に酸化されると先ほど言いました
and then cause this inflammatory response
そしてこの炎症反応を引き起こします
If it can prevent it from oxidizing
酸化を防ぐことができれば
maybe this helps
おそらくこれは役立つでしょう
That's more to do with inflammation
それはむしろ炎症と関係があります
This is a kind of regionalized silver, this is Kinokain
これは一種の地域化されたシルバーです、これがキノカインです
So this company is making this Kinokain not work
つまり、この会社はこのキノカインを機能させないようにしているのです
And this monocyte will not have
そして、この単球には
It will not enter the study of learning, nor will it enter this class
それは学習の研究にも入りませんし、このクラスにも入りません
So this is still in the second issue
これはまだ第 2 号にあります
The last paragraph is the relationship with Cancer
最後の段落はがんとの関係です。
I think this must be
これはきっとそうだと思います
Fort de la Léz cancer is now our
フォート・デ・ラ・レスのがんは今や私たちの問題です
is the most difficult
最も難しいです
a disease of the handle
handle的一個疾病
Also most in need of research development
研究開発も最も必要とされている
and then hope to get a well-developed drug
そしてよく開発された薬を手に入れることを期待しています
This Cancer is indeed
このガンはまさに
In the past many years, I did not think of the relationship with Information
ここ数年、私は情報との関係について考えていませんでした。
But now, you look at the textbook
でも今、教科書を見てみると、
clearly written
明確に書かれた
That is, Information is a very important role of the website.
つまり、情報はウェブサイトの非常に重要な役割です。
play a very big role
非常に大きな役割を果たします
there are two points
2つの点があります
one is in that
一つはその中にあります
In case of chronic inflammation
慢性炎症の場合
Cancel will develop
キャンセルは発展します
For example H.Pylo-E
たとえば、H.Pylo-E
Helicopter-Pylo-E inside the stomach
胃の中のヘリコプター Pylo-E
This can cause gastritis
胃炎を引き起こす可能性があります
But if it is said that this treatment is not removed
でも、この治療法が外れないと言われたら
Over time, some people
時間が経つと、人によっては
Among many people, he will know about gastric cancer
胃がんについては多くの人が知っているだろう
That's another Inflammatory Bowel Disease
それも炎症性腸疾患です
Just inside the Colon
コロンのすぐ内側
it will have long term information
長期的な情報が含まれます
This is in a small number of patients
これは患者数が少ない
It will end up with Colon Rectocancin
最終的には結腸レクトカンシンになります
Then in Taiwan, it is more often Hepatitis
それから台湾では肝炎がより頻繁に発生します
Hepatitis B or C
B型またはC型肝炎
This causes viral infection
これがウイルス感染の原因となる
followed by an inflammatory response
続いて炎症反応が起こる
when it comes to the end
最後になると
Some patients develop hepatitis and liver cancer
肝炎や肝がんを発症する患者もいる
It's an inflammatory reaction
それは炎症反応です
after becoming a chronic inflammatory reaction
慢性炎症反応になった後
In some cases it can also cause CANS
場合によっては、CANS を引き起こす可能性もあります
So this is the first example of the relationship between inflammation and CANS
これが炎症とCANSの関係の最初の例です
If you draw it here, you will be a good boy.
ここに描けばいい子になれるよ。
Here is an inflammatory reaction
これが炎症反応です
That should be a normal cell
それは正常な細胞のはずです
it turns into cancer cells
ガン細胞に変わってしまいます
That's why it's like this in detail
ということで詳しくはこんな感じです
not entirely clear
完全には明らかではない
But what we know is that these inflammatory reactions
しかし、私たちが知っているのは、これらの炎症反応は
some inflammatory factors
いくつかの炎症因子
Can cause some genetic changes in this normal cell
この正常な細胞に何らかの遺伝的変化を引き起こす可能性があります
For example mutation
たとえば突然変異
After the mutation is generated
突然変異が発生した後
This cell becomes a cancer cell
この細胞はがん細胞になります
The other relationship with the inflammatory response is
また、炎症反応との関係は、
After becoming a cancer cell
がん細胞になってから
Surrounding cancer cells is an inflamed
周囲のがん細胞が炎症を起こしている
is an inflamed
炎症を起こしている
is a response to inflammation inside
内部の炎症に対する反応です
How does that cause an inflammatory reaction?
それはどのようにして炎症反応を引き起こすのでしょうか？
not entirely clear
完全には明らかではない
But of course cancer cells secrete a lot of
しかし、もちろん、がん細胞は多くの物質を分泌します。
Even what I just said was Sedkar
私が今言ったことさえセドカールだった
Chimocha will be secreted
チモカが分泌される
so it attracts these
だからそれはこれらを引き寄せます
these inflammatory reactions
これらの炎症反応
Some people say that cancer is like an injury that cannot be cured
がんは治らない怪我のようなものだと言う人もいます
So the host is always thinking about repairing it
したがって、ホストは常にそれを修復することを考えています
repair it is the reaction of pronunciation around here
修復 ここら辺の発音の対応です
Then we knew about cancer in the past
それから私たちは過去に癌について知っていました
It is continuing to reproduce in it
その中で再現し続けている
and its cells are less likely to die
そしてその細胞は死ぬ可能性が低くなります
so let's just say
だから言ってみよう
let's just talk
ただ話しましょう
Cells are less likely to die
細胞が死ぬ可能性が低くなります
Then cancer it needs blood vessels
がんには血管が必要です
to supply it with oxygen
酸素を供給するために
or its nutrient
またはその栄養素
Then it also knows how to
それから、それはまた、方法を知っています
make new blood vessels
新しい血管を作る
then its immune system
それからその免疫システム
Society sees cancer cells
社会はがん細胞を観察する
and want to remove it
そしてそれを削除したい
But cancer cells also know what to look like
しかし、がん細胞もどのように見えるかを知っています
Evade elimination by immune cells
免疫細胞による排除を回避する
But now we know that when you put in the persistent chronic inflammation
しかし今では、持続的な慢性炎症が続くと、
Right around this Cancel, it has been chronically inflamed
このキャンセルのあたりで慢性的に炎症を起こしています
And this chronic inflammation, as mentioned just now, it will cause the gene to have mutation
そして、この慢性炎症は、先ほども触れたように、遺伝子に変異を生じさせます。
At the same time, it will promote the proliferation of this cancer cell just now
同時に、今このがん細胞の増殖を促進します。
It promotes the formation of blood vessels
血管の形成を促進します
And then finally, hepatitis, and finally that cancer cell washes into nearby cells
そして最後に肝炎、そして最後にそのがん細胞が近くの細胞に流れ込みます
In the end, it will spread, the factors of these inflammatory reactions
最終的には広がる、これらの炎症反応の要因
or its cells will facilitate this process
またはその細胞がこのプロセスを促進します
So this is a great idea that inflammation leads to cancer, now a thought
炎症が癌につながるというのは素晴らしい考えですが、今では考えられています
If this is the case, then see medicine, can inflammation medicine be useful in treating cancer?
これが事実であれば、薬を見てください。炎症薬は癌の治療に役立ちますか?
This is indeed the case, it is IceBrain, the medicine we use very often
これはまさにその通りです。私たちが頻繁に使用する薬、IceBrain です。
we know it looks inflammatory
炎症を起こしているように見えることはわかっています
Therefore, in a clinical trial
したがって、臨床試験では
visible
見える
we know we probably
私たちはおそらく知っています
Should be after the age of 50
50歳以降であるべき
can eat spring
春を食べられる
otherwise eat a small amount
それ以外の場合は少量を食べる
So some people have eaten spring
だから春を食べた人もいる
I have eaten it for more than 20 years
20年以上食べています
It plays a role in the risk of colorectal cancer
結腸直腸がんのリスクに関与します
It is indeed less than no food
それは確かに食べ物がないよりも少ないです
30% 40%
３０％ ４０％
So this is a
これは
Proved to be inflamed on coffee
コーヒーで炎症を起こすことが判明
can be slightly reduced
わずかに減らすことができます
cancer cancer
がん がん
A Proof of the Rate of Interest
金利の証明
Of course more research is needed
もちろんさらなる研究が必要です
work to learn more about this
これについてもっと学ぶために取り組んでください
Also this is right
これも正しい
prostaglandins
前列腺素
Looks like inflammation medicine
炎症の薬みたい
In fact it's endosterol
実はエンドステロールなのです
These two words are more commonly used
この 2 つの単語はより一般的に使用されます
from arthritis
関節炎から
for pain
痛みのために
It is now clinically proven
現在では臨床的に証明されています
In fact, it is helpful in the treatment of cancer
実はガンの治療にも効果があるのです
I think this is the last one
これが最後だと思う
Finally, I would like to thank the postdoctoral students in the laboratory
最後に、研究室のポスドクの学生たちに感謝したいと思います。
This is the first preparation
これが最初の準備です
It is the material I gave to the research institute of National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学の研究機関に提供した資料です
For this popular science speech
この人気の科学スピーチについて
Please help me change it to a more popular word
もっと人気のある言葉に変更するのを手伝ってください
Then the most important thing is to put Chinese in
それから最も重要なことは中国語を入れることです
Because in the United States for many years
なぜなら、長年アメリカにいたからです。
So if I speak Chinese, I need someone else to translate for me.
そのため、中国語の翻訳を他の人に頼る必要があります。
then thank them
それから彼らに感謝します
Thank you for your attention
ご清聴ありがとうございました
Thanks
ありがとう
we are very grateful
私たちはとても感謝しています
And Liu Shouchang went from a good inflammatory reaction to a bad inflammatory reaction
そして、Liu Shouchang は良い炎症反応から悪い炎症反応に移行しました
Even Bad Inflammation Causes Common Diseases in Our Humans
悪い炎症でも人間の一般的な病気の原因となる
we often talk
私たちはよく話します
What are the two most important causes of death in Taiwan?
台湾における最も重要な死因は何ですか?
The number one cause of death is cancer
死因の第1位はガン
The second leading cause of death is heart disease and stroke
死因の第2位は心臓病と脳卒中
So in fact we used to think that
実際、私たちは以前は次のように考えていました
These things like cancer cardiovascular disease
がん、心血管疾患など
Nothing to do with inflammation
炎症とは関係ない
Now after we listened to Chief Liu's speech today
今日の劉署長のスピーチを聞いてから
I know that these common human diseases
私はこれらの一般的な人間の病気を知っています
A very important cause of death is also related to inflammation
非常に重要な死因も炎症に関連しています
We thank Chief Liu for his speech
劉長官のスピーチに感謝します
Now we follow net profit
次に純利益を追跡します
time for some Q&A
質疑応答の時間
everyone can ask
誰もが尋ねることができます
Then we will ask Chief Liu to answer with you
それでは、劉長官にお答えいただきます。
OK
OK
is there anything please
何かありますか？
ask questions
質問をする
Please use the microphone and introduce yourself
マイクを使って自己紹介をしてください
okay thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
Hello, Mr. Liu
こんにちは、劉さん。
Institute of Medical Informatics, Taipei Medical University
台北医科大学医療情報学研究所
One problem is that I didn't seem to specifically mention it just now.
一つ問題は、今特に言及しなかったようです。
It is also related to speech
スピーチにも関係してきます
But it's an autoimmune disease
しかし自己免疫疾患
So derived from this
ここから派生したもの
Autoimmunity should always be irregular
自己免疫は常に不規則でなければなりません
There have been some informational speeches somewhere in the
どこかで情報提供のスピーチが行われました。
Will he be related to the Egyptian government because of this?
このために彼はエジプト政府と関係があるのでしょうか？
Thanks
ありがとう
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
Yes, autoimmunity was a very important one at the time
はい、自己免疫は当時非常に重要なものでした
is the immune system
免疫システムです
some are too strong
いくつかは強すぎる
Then he shouldn't be affected
そうすれば彼は影響を受けないはずだ
For example, to our own cells
たとえば、私たち自身の細胞に
usually should not have immunity
通常は免疫がないはずです
but there is no control
しかし制御はありません
So in the case of 4
つまり4の場合は
to ourselves
自分たちに
own cells generate immunity
自分自身の細胞が免疫を生成する
Of course this is
もちろんこれは
In addition to responding to the speech
スピーチに答えるだけでなく、
He is also closely related
彼も密接な関係にあります
Then this one is also immune
じゃあこれも免疫あるよ
As for the relationship with the sea
海との関わりについても
As far as I know it's not that obvious
私の知る限り、それはそれほど明らかではありません
some have , in fact there are
あるものはあります、実際にはあります
in fact there is
実際にはあります
then i have to tell
それなら言わなければなりません
good question you said
あなたが言った良い質問
For example, hand cancer, liver cancer
例：手のがん、肝臓がん
I don't see it so far
今のところ見えない
that cancer
その癌
For example, liver cancer is an inflammation of the skin
たとえば、肝臓がんは皮膚の炎症です。
But it did not increase the incentives for skin cancer
しかし、皮膚がんの誘因は増加しませんでした
So it's not exactly one-to-one
厳密には1対1ではないので、
So what about autoimmunity?
では、自己免疫についてはどうでしょうか？
Some autoimmunity does not mean more cancer
一部の自己免疫はがんの増加を意味しない
but some words are
しかし、いくつかの言葉は
For example, there is a thing called Polymycitis
たとえば、多発性真菌炎というものがあります。
So an autoimmune response in the muscles
つまり、筋肉における自己免疫反応
that inside
中のそれ
The motivation of that cancer is very high
そのガンの動機は非常に高い
right
右
I will teach you a few steps to solve it
それを解決するためのいくつかの手順を教えます
just go ahead and answer your questions
質問に答えてください
come on this side
こちら側に来てください
ask the director
監督に聞いてください
Director just mentioned about liver gland
先ほど局長が肝腺のことをおっしゃいました。
What is the difference between hepatic gland and odorous dermatitis
肝腺と臭気性皮膚炎の違いは何ですか
Thanks
ありがとう
these two are different
この二つは違います
One is the liver gland is the love is
一つは肝腺、愛は
The odor is A.Towelge-Metallis
匂いはA.Towelge-Metallisです
These are two different
これは2つの違いです
completely different disease
全く別の病気
and it can be distinguished
そしてそれは区別できる
Slicing is usually less needed
通常不太需要切片
you can see
見ることができます
That is to look at its shape on the one hand
それは一方ではその形を見ることです
So called morphology
いわゆる形態学
As for its cause
その原因については
have to be the same
同じでなければなりません
that's clean
それはきれいです
Odor allergic dermatitis
臭気アレルギー性皮膚炎
I just told you
私はちょうどあなたに言いました
With that B.M.
そのBMとは
related to asthma
喘息に関連した
What about immunity
免疫力はどうでしょうか
Let's just say this with
これだけ言ってみましょう
With that D2 TH2
そのD2 TH2で
T cells
T細胞
Type II related
タイプⅡ関連
What about liver cancer
肝臓がんはどうでしょうか
it is now
それは今です
In the past we thought it was TH50,000
以前はTH50,000だと思っていました
Type I
タイプI
But now it is clear that it is
しかし今ではそれが明らかである
another one
もう一つ
The other one talks more and more
もう一人はどんどん話していきます
specialized
専門化された
TH7T related
TH7T関連
Yes these two are different mechanisms
はい、これら 2 つは異なるメカニズムです
Affecting
影響的
different etiologies
さまざまな病因
right
右
Just mentioned that liver cancer
先ほど肝臓がんのことを言いました
It is good for liver cancer
肝臓がんに良い
what moisturizing lotion and that steroid
保湿ローションとステロイドは何ですか
dermatitis that signifies
鼻皮膚炎
Is it also necessary to use quality
品質も必要ですか？
Yes, just a few medicines
はい、薬を少しだけ
almost all can be used
ほぼ全て使える
right
右
That is to say, on liver cancer
つまり、肝臓がんについては、
use
用的
especially if internal alcohol
特に体内アルコールの場合
is in
いる
emblematic dermatitis
意味性皮膚炎
is available
利用可能です
Then what
じゃあ何
Illuminated
イルミネーション付き
The same goes for ultraviolet light
紫外線も同様です
It can be used for dermatitis and liver cancer
皮膚炎や肝臓がんにも使用できます
That's a pity that these
それは残念です、これらは
These so-called Biotic
これらのいわゆるバイオティック
that is currently in
それは現在入っています
on allergic dermatitis
アレルギー性皮膚炎について
not yet
まだ
no other medicine
他の薬はありません
So progress on clean is much faster than that
したがって、クリーンの進歩はそれよりもはるかに速いです
Thanks
ありがとう
In principle, I am an ordinary citizen
基本的に私は一般国民です
i want to ask a question
私は質問をしたいです
We just mentioned this term from the inflammation industry
炎症業界のこの用語について言及したところです
Then the general treatment with drugs
その後は薬による一般的な治療となります。
Inflammation is a principle code anti-hours
炎症は時間に対する原則的なコードです
Its ties to this inflamed industry
この炎上する業界とのつながり
What Actually Affects Inflammatory Industry Relationships
炎症を起こす業界関係に実際に影響を与えるもの
This school question asks if you are
この学校の質問は、あなたが次のようなことをしているかどうかを尋ねます。
This is what we talk about to see vitamins
今回はビタミンについてのお話です
usually a bacterial infection
通常は細菌感染症
shall we use it again
また利用しましょうか
So the first one is
最初のものは
If there is a bacterial infection
細菌感染がある場合
Look at the antibiotics to get rid of the bacteria
細菌を取り除くための抗生物質を調べてください
Of course there were bacteria next.
もちろん次は細菌でした。
bacteria can cause
細菌が原因となる可能性があります
Initiation reaction
開始反応
Since you don't have bacteria
菌がいないから
There will be no reaction at the source
ソースでは反応がありません
so here's an idea
そこでアイデアです
This is what we really see as numbers
これが私たちが実際に数字として見ているものです
but
しかし
in fact
実際には
We now know a lot about numbers
私たちは今、数字について多くのことを知っています
It has the effect of looking at the origin
原点を見つめる効果がある
it depends on the role of origin
それは起源の役割に依存します
so i don't want you guys
だから私はあなたたちを欲しくない
Do you have
ありますか
Is it Echme please wait
エクメですか、お待ちください
that that
それは
it's the usual way
それはいつものやり方です
slightly more serious
もう少し深刻な
Is to use antibiotics
抗生物質を使うことです
use that as a number
それを数字として使う
In fact it works
実際、それは機能します
Not exactly because it's bacterial drying
細菌による乾燥が原因ではありません
It actually has bacteria
実は菌がいる
Will cause
原因となります
Echme
エクメ
But its function is
しかし、その機能は、
it looks at origin
それは原点を見ます
So there are a lot of viewers
なので視聴者も多いですよ
There is a function to see the origin
原点を見る機能があります
So these two reasons
したがって、この 2 つの理由は、
is itself
それ自体です
There is a function to see the origin
原点を見る機能があります
I think that explains your problem
それがあなたの問題を説明していると思います
I'm sorry, sir, I'll ask you a little more.
すみません、先生、もう少しお聞きしたいのですが。
Just now you said dry and salty is for life
さっき君は、乾燥と塩辛さは一生ものだと言いましたね
no way to eat fish
魚を食べる方法がない
Is there any way to eat fish with the smelly skin?
皮が臭い魚を食べる方法はありますか？
Because now is the picture just drawn
今は描いたばかりの絵だから
So it's okay, maybe 60 to 70% of children
だから大丈夫、おそらく60～70％の子供たちは
By the age of ten or so, there will be no
10歳くらいまでには、
sometimes come out later
時々後から出てくる
But one time it will get lighter and lighter
でも一度はどんどん軽くなっていきます
in the end not even
結局はさえない
So it's more dry and salty than long-term
長期保存よりもドライで塩辛いです
Sixty to seventy percent of odorous skin
皮膚の臭いの60～70％
will not continue the opportunity
機会は続かないでしょう
It's gone when you reach adulthood
大人になったらなくなるよ
But my child is already in his twenties and thirties
でも、うちの子はもう20代、30代です
That's a pity to be in those 30s again
また30代に戻るのは残念だ
So how can this be said to be questioned?
では、どうしてこれが疑問視されていると言えるでしょうか？
Then questioning is like asking dry salty
その場合、質問することは無味乾燥で塩辛い質問をするようなものです
take medicine, keep taking medicine
薬を飲んで、薬を飲み続けてください
That is, so far, most of them are not compatible with that, and that is lighting
つまり、今のところほとんどがそれに対応していない、それが照明です
Illuminated
イルミネーション付き
So there is a chance that odorous dermatitis can be cured
つまり臭い皮膚炎は治る可能性がある
So it's me, it's me
だから、それは私です、それは私です
Pharmaceutical companies in this area usually do not do much because most of the children have
この分野の製薬会社は通常、ほとんどの子供たちが病気であるため、あまり何もしません。
Then also know that they will be gone after a while
そして、しばらくすると彼らがいなくなることも知ってください
So it's a little bit more difficult for him to do clinical work in the children's department, yes.
ですから、彼にとって小児科で臨床の仕事をするのは少し難しいのです、はい。
So usually, the one here usually cooks a lot more than dry and salty stir-fry
通常、ここのものは、乾燥した塩味の炒め物よりもはるかに多くの料理を作ることが多いです
But I believe so, now but I can mention that
でも、今はそう信じていますが、一つ言えるのは、
There is still gallbladder cleansing, the amine tire IGE just mentioned
胆嚢の洗浄、先ほどIGEが言及したアミンタイヤがまだ残っています。
In fact, it is helpful for dermatitis, and it can be used
実際、皮膚炎に効果があり、使用できます。
So odorous dermatitis will fade with age
加齢とともに臭い皮膚炎は消えていくので
It's different, it's when I was a kid, when I was a kid
それは違う、それは私が子供の頃、私が子供の頃
But grown-ups still sometimes, sometimes
でも大人だって時々、時々
I think there will always be
必ずあると思うよ
Yes, not necessarily clear
はい、必ずしも明確ではありません
not necessarily clear
必ずしも明確ではない
Thanks
ありがとう
Thank you for sharing
共有していただきありがとうございます
what you just said
あなたが今言ったこと
50 years old or R10P person
50歳以上またはR10Pの方
Will reduce the suspicious rate of colorectal cancer
結腸直腸がんの疑いのある割合を減らします
That said, after colorectal cancer surgery
とは言え、大腸がんの手術後は
eat R10P people
R10Pの人を食べる
Will it reduce hair care rate
ヘアケア率は低下しますか
I don't know if there is any data here
ここにデータがあるかどうかはわかりません
I don't know if there is
あるかどうかは分かりません
yes it is still possible
はい、まだ可能です
but i want aesthrin to eat
でもエスリンには食べてもらいたい
i want to be there
私はそこに行きたいです
heart attack by that bath
その風呂で心臓発作
It's obvious from the top of the heavy madness
重い狂気の上から見ても明らかだ
So I also say this reason
だから私もこの理由を言います
That's why I think it's edible
だから食べられると思う
low dose
低用量
in that
その中で
The words above cancer
がんの上の言葉
Not saying it's 100 percent, it's just lowering the force.
100パーセントとは言えませんが、力が下がっているだけです。
That data is quite obvious
そのデータは非常に明白です
Only in the case of this complex flowering
この複雑な開花の場合にのみ
I don't think there's any data on this right now
現時点ではこれに関するデータはないと思います
I knew it
私はそれを知っていました
ask the director
監督に聞いてください
in terms of allergies
アレルギーの面では
Is there any way for that IG part
そのIG部分を利用する方法はありますか
Like exercising or avoiding drugs
運動や薬物の回避など
You can increase the possibility of IG
IGの可能性を高めることができます
This is the birth of this IG
これがこのIGの誕生です
I guess there's always no downside in sports
スポーツには常にマイナス面なんてないんだと思う
as long as you don't get hurt
怪我をしない限り
but on sensitive
しかしセンシティブでは
haven't said yes yet
まだ「はい」と言っていません
But movement is, on the one hand, e.g.
しかし、一方では動きもあります。
if you are overweight
太りすぎの場合
Sometimes asthma is related to OBCT
喘息が OBCT に関連している場合もあります
So exercise less
だから運動量も減って
is to reduce it
それを減らすことです
These indirect effects on health
健康に対するこれらの間接的な影響
this should help
これは役立つはずです
But for the generation of this IG
しかし、このIGの世代にとっては
These inflammatory mechanisms are sensitive to this
これらの炎症メカニズムはこれに敏感です
As far as I know it doesn't say it will decrease
私の知る限りでは減るとは言えません
yes
はい
right
右
sultan ask
スルタンは尋ねる
Just now when you mentioned the allergic reaction
先ほどアレルギー反応について言及したとき
mast cells
肥満細胞
Does this mast cell mean fat cell?
このマスト細胞というのは脂肪細胞のことなのでしょうか？
Then it's inflammation and obesity
それから炎症と肥満です
with the one you just mentioned
あなたが今言ったものと一緒に
between cardiovascular disease and cancer
心血管疾患とがんの間
What is its cause and effect relationship?
その因果関係は何でしょうか？
Thanks
ありがとう
That is not this mast cell is Massal
それはこの肥満細胞がマッサルではありません
you said fat
あなたは太っていると言った
In fact, I'm obese, I think you're obese
実際、私は肥満です、あなたも肥満だと思います
may refer to fat cells
脂肪細胞を指す場合もあります
And the point gill
そしてポイントギル
those are two different
それらは二つ違います
obesity
肥満
It is mast cell, it is Mass cell
それはマスト細胞です、それはマス細胞です
Then it is quite a unique cell
それは非常にユニークな細胞です
It really has something to do with that sensitivity
それは本当にその感性と関係があります
It is what makes the inside of our human body
それが私たち人間の体の内部を作っているのです
Probably this cell will produce Histamine
おそらくこの細胞はヒスタミンを生成するでしょう
I know this Nutriphia also produces
このニュートリフィアも生産していることは知っています
but so far
しかし、これまでのところ
Probably what the textbook said is Histamine
おそらく教科書に書いてあるのはヒスタミンだと思われます
All Mass cells are produced by mast cells
すべてのマス細胞はマスト細胞によって生成されます
But this mast cell
しかしこの肥満細胞は
It is actually in other diseases
実は他の病気にもあるんです
There will be, there will be, and there will be
あるでしょう、あるでしょう、そしてあるでしょう
even in cancer
癌でも
Mass cell also does research
Mass Cellも研究を行っています
Mass cell has also been researched in the generation of cancer
大量細胞は癌の発生にも研究されています
Also found that Mass cell will be effective
マスセルが効果的であることも判明
Will contribute to the generation of cancer
がんの発生に寄与することになる
So it does a lot
それで、それはたくさんのことをします
But it is more researched
しかし、それはさらに研究されています
is a sensitive reaction
敏感な反応です
Sensitive reactions are very many
敏感な反応が非常に多い
very obvious function
非常に明白な機能
later
後で
here first
まずはここで
Usually when we go to see a doctor
通常、私たちが医師の診察を受けるとき、
The doctor will tell you to take some anti-inflammatory drugs
医者はあなたに抗炎症薬を飲むように言うでしょう
According to ordinary people, the practice of turning the wheel
一般の人によると、車輪を回す練習は、
So are anti-inflammatory drugs antibiotics or
抗炎症薬や抗生物質も同様です。
still sweating
まだ汗をかいている
Let the common people understand your
一般の人たちにもあなたの考えを理解してもらいましょう
The confusion is which one is called an anti-inflammatory drug
混乱しているのは、どれが抗炎症薬と呼ばれるかです。
I don't have that kind of experience
そんな経験ないけど
so we know
だから私たちは知っています
Speaking of anti-inflammatory drugs
抗炎症薬といえば
Anti-inflammatory drugs are here
抗炎症薬はここにあります
What kind of say an example is what
例としてはどのようなものが挙げられるでしょうか
as we just said
今言ったように
is undaefermetary medicine
不法医学です
there are some
幾つかある
especially in taiwan
特に台湾では
many people say
多くの人が言う
There are some
幾つかある
inflammatory reactions are some
炎症反応はいくつかあります
this anti-inflammatory drug
この抗炎症薬は
that's something like
それは次のようなものです
Aspirin
アスピリン
or something like
またはそのようなもの
to some of these
これらのいくつかに
Some anti-inflammatory drugs like steroids
ステロイドなどの一部の抗炎症薬
These are the ones that are often opened in China.
これらは中国でよく開かれているものです。
there is such a medicine
そんな薬があります
Now the question just now is
さて、今の質問は、
Are these anti-inflammatory drugs?
これらは抗炎症薬ですか？
Since it's inflammation, it's not good
炎症だからダメだよ
Then there will be all kinds of inflammation
その後、あらゆる種類の炎症が発生します
So should we take some anti-inflammatory drugs?
それでは、抗炎症薬を服用したほうがよいのでしょうか？
anti-inflammatory drugs
抗炎症薬
Like Aspirin is a particle
アスピリンが粒子のようなもの
Particles like Tylenol
タイレノールのような粒子
Tylenol is an inflammatory
タイレノールは炎症性物質です
is anti-inflammatory
抗炎症作用がある
Right, so that's probably a
そうです、それはおそらく
Then there shouldn't be any harm in that.
そうすれば、何も害はないはずです。
should be no harm
害がないはずです
Of course the most effective anti-inflammation is the inner bone hip
もちろん、最も効果的な抗炎症は股関節の内側の骨です。
You can still eat when necessary
必要に応じて食べることもできます
For that fork, we usually
そのフォークについては、通常、
As long as there is no residual error
残留誤差がない限り
actually helps
実際に役立ちます
But if you look at the speech, these words
しかし、スピーチを見てみると、これらの言葉は、
I think it depends on what kind of disease it is.
どういう病気かによると思います。
yes what kind of disease
はい、どんな病気ですか
If it is pain in these joints
この関節の痛みなら
If talking about watching speeches
スピーチを見ることについて話すなら
Probably this Ib Profit
おそらくこのIb利益
or memory
または記憶
or Tylenol
またはタイレノール
There seems to be a problem behind that
その裏には問題がありそうだ
there is a problem with this
これには問題があります
Please ask me for a long time
久々に聞いてください
Current use of allergy medications
現在のアレルギー薬の使用
Which one works better
どちらがより良く機能しますか
As for the extent of his side effects
彼の副作用の程度については
Is there any use of this aspect in traditional Chinese medicine?
伝統的な中国医学でこの側面を活用することはありますか?
Thanks
ありがとう
When you say allergic, you mean like Bn
アレルギーって言うのはBnのようなことを指します
Yes, Bn's words
そう、Bnさんの言葉です
Bn is still Antihistimum so far
Bnは今のところまだ抗ヒスチム薬です
It is the main medicine
主なお薬です
But if necessary, use internal bone storage
ただし、必要に応じて、内部ボーン ストレージを使用します。
But if it is slight, most Anti-Hismis can be
しかし、それが軽度であれば、ほとんどのアンチヒスミスは、
As for, for example, Anti-IG
たとえば、アンチIGについては、
I think it should be very useful
とても役立つはずだと思います
But it's a bit like killing a chicken with a bull's knife
でもそれは雄牛のナイフで鶏を殺すようなものです
of course something
もちろん事情もありますよ
especially you are very very sad
特にあなたはとてもとても悲しいです
is edible
食用です
But then it becomes the so-called off-level
しかし、それはいわゆるオフレベルになります
Because the U.S. Department of Health
なぜなら、米国保健省は、
Didn't say it was proof
証拠だとは言ってない
This is the thing to avoid smoking
禁煙すべきはこれだ
It is Azema
アゼマです
But Moderny-Civill
しかし、Moderny-Civill
but in the US
しかし米国では
Used in non-Moderny-Civill-Azema
非Moderny-Civill-Azemaで使用
I think there are still many people using
まだまだ使っている人も多いと思います
but if it is slight
しかしそれが軽度であれば
if it's not that serious
そこまで深刻でないなら
I don't think you need to use this
これを使う必要はないと思います
use this
これを使って
It is because of those biological
それはそれらの生物学的理由によるものです
is quite expensive
かなり高価です
The annual fee is in US dollars
年会費は米ドルです
Ten thousand and twenty thousand
上一萬兩萬
I have to say that I just mentioned a lot of scientific names and company names
先ほどたくさんの学名や企業名を挙げましたが、
I really have no conflict
本当に矛盾がないんだよ
No
いいえ
I don't have that stock
その在庫はありません
Neither do I. I'm not and I'm not the one who invented it.
私もそうではありません。私はそれを発明した人でもありません。
There are many types of allergies
アレルギーにはたくさんの種類があります
some are cheap and some are expensive
安いものもあれば高いものもあります
A tribute to some creatures like the ones just mentioned
先ほど述べたようないくつかの生き物へのオマージュ
anti-IgE antibodies
抗IgE抗体
actually
実際
Insufficient not very severe symptoms of severe asthma
重度の喘息のそれほど重度ではない症状が不十分
But to use that medicine
でもその薬を使うには
as we say
私たちが言うように
Is it worth it to spend a lot of money?
多額のお金を費やす価値はありますか？
Of course, the health insurance will not be given based on Taiwan's history.
もちろん、台湾の歴史に基づいて健康保険は適用されません。
Because your disease is not serious enough to need this drug
あなたの病気はこの薬を必要とするほど深刻ではないため
is a general allergic reaction
一般的なアレルギー反応です
Or anti-organism drugs, etc.
あるいは抗微生物薬など。
General health insurance will give
一般的な健康保険が適用されます
but if to
しかし、もしそうするなら
bio tribute section
バイオトリビュートセクション
In the case of Taiwan's health insurance, the possibility of giving is probably very low
台湾の健康保険の場合、給付される可能性は非常に低いと思われます
unless it's serious like
それが深刻でない限り
Teresa Teng's severe asthma
テレサテンの重度の喘息
Then this kind of medicine is likely to be needed at this time.
そうすると、現時点ではこの種の薬が必要になる可能性があります。
I'll come here first, okay?
まずここに来ます、いいですか？
That's what I want to ask, I just talked about SARS
それが私が聞きたいことです、先ほどSARSについて話しました
It is because of the strong inflammation that destroys
破壊するのは強い炎症のためです
The tissue of the lungs means SARS
肺の組織はSARSを意味します
The disease itself is not because the virus is too strong
病気自体はウイルスが強すぎるからではない
It's because of the inflammatory response he caused
それは彼が引き起こした炎症反応のせいです
Does it harm the human body? If you want something else, just ask again.
人体に害はありますか? 他に欲しいことがあれば、もう一度質問してください。
Does he have any other diseases like SARS
彼はSARSのような他の病気を持っていますか
Thank you, good question, that's exactly what it looks like
ありがとう、いい質問ですね、まさにその通りです
Is his virus particularly strong? It's hard to say
彼のウイルスは特に強いのでしょうか? それはわかりません
Because it is completely determined by who is our body
それは私たちの体が誰であるかによって完全に決まるからです
right , or that in this case
そうですね、この場合はそれです
His at least we know is the cause of death
少なくとも我々が知っている彼の死因は
It's because our body reacts too strongly
それは身体が過剰に反応するからです
What part of our body sees him
私たちの体のどの部分が彼を認識しているのか
Why do you know it's a virus
なぜウイルスだとわかるのですか
different from other viruses
他のウイルスとは違う
so we want more reactions
だからもっと反応が欲しいです
to be able to resist, to be able to resist
抵抗できる、抵抗できる
is it because of this
このせいですか？
I guess this aspect is not so clear
この辺はあまり明確ではないと思います
We are just down to the end result
最終結果を待つばかりです
it is indeed the cause of the final death
それは確かに最終的な死の原因です
or the cause of the sickness
あるいは病気の原因
because we react a little too much
ちょっと反応しすぎだから
but we have no control
しかし私たちにはコントロールできません
we didn't say yes
私たちは「はい」とは言いませんでした
If the same person doesn't react so much
同じ人があまり反応しない場合
will there be a problem
問題はありますか
there is a problem not sure
よくわからない問題があります
remind me of a
を思い出させてください
I didn't mention it
それについては言及しませんでした
If we know more about this
これについてもっと知っていれば
In fact, these self-supporting organisms
実際、これらは自助努力以来です。
maybe useful
たぶん役に立つ
We know what's in SARS
私たちは SARS の正体を知っています
Cause this Sidecans stone
だってこのサイドカンストーン
words we now know
私たちが今知っている言葉
Then prevention is
そうすると予防は
Now I hear in the Middle East
今、中東で聞いています
It seems that there are several cases
いくつかのケースがあるようです
It seems that there are 45 cases
45件あるそうです
Then two people in the family died
その後、家族２人が亡くなった
If there is another SARS
またSARSが流行ったら
If so
もしそうなら
Maybe Anti-TNF
おそらく抗TNF
Give a few injections, at that time, if you give it impromptu, maybe it will be useful
数回の注射、その時、即席注射、もしかしたら役に立つかもしれない
Is it right, and these two questions are
そうですか、そしてこれら 2 つの質問は
Are there any other diseases similar to SARS?
SARSに似た病気は他にもありますか?
I think liver cancer is liver cancer
肝臓がんは肝臓がんだと思います
It is HEP-10, heterosexual hepatitis
HEP-10、異性間性肝炎です
In the beginning, especially type A, it's not chronic
初期、特にA型は慢性的ではない
When it's improvised, it's kind of causing physical sickness
即興でやるとなんだか体調が悪くなる
actually an inflammatory response
実は炎症反応
There's a problem here, come on, from here, wait on this side
ここに問題がある、さあ、ここから、こちら側で待ってください
I'm talking to the general public, please ask
一般の方に向けて話しているので聞いてください
Just now the president mentioned that some people have immune systems
先ほど大統領は、免疫システムを持っている人もいると述べました
If it is stimulated by some foreign materials and causes damage, it will produce immunity
何らかの異物の刺激を受けてダメージを受けると、免疫が生成されます。
It is IG1, which accepts the chemical cognition that produces certain specific stimuli
ある特定の刺激を生み出す化学的認知を受け入れるのがIG1です。
then it will put the layered runny race, eye rewrite
それからそれは層状の鼻水レースを置きます、目を書き換えます
just some people wrong
一部の人が間違っているだけ
fault
障害
I want to ask the director
監督に聞きたい
can be specific
具体的にすることができる
The stimulus of foreign materials
異物の刺激
which aspect
どの面
Is it the stimulation of foreign materials?
異物の刺激でしょうか？
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
I just wrote an allergen
アレルギー物質を書きました
Allergens are all around us
アレルゲンは私たちの周りに存在します
like pollen
花粉のように
then drugs
それから麻薬
and dusty
そして埃っぽい
are foreign
外国人です
these words
これらの単語
In fact, even if we can eat it
実際、食べられるとしても、
none of us will have a problem
私たちの誰も問題はありません
especially if say
特に言うなら
If we don't have such a sensitive constitution
そんなに敏感な体質でなければ
these we will react to it
これらに私たちは反応します
but not sensitive
しかし敏感ではない
but some people
しかし一部の人は
His physique is like this
彼の体格はこんな感じです
maybe it has something to do with clothes
もしかしたら服装と関係があるかもしれない
just accept this time
今回だけは受け入れてください
Our body has a reaction to it
私たちの体はそれに反応します
The result of the reaction produces IGE
反応の結果、IGEが生成されます
IGE in turn causes sensitive
IGEは今度は過敏症を引き起こす
It's just that you just said that you have these symptoms
さっきこんな症状があるって言ってたよ
That's because IGE
それはIGEだからです
I take the same pollen of these I don't generate IG
私はこれらと同じ花粉を摂取しますが、IGは生成しません
But you generate IG, the difference is here like this
しかし、IGを生成すると、違いは次のようになります
this is what these are humlist
これがこれらが謙虚なものです
It should be that we don't need to specifically react to it
特に反応する必要はないはずです
but we are responsive
しかし、私たちは反応します
And in some people, its reaction is to cause IG
そして人によっては、その反応がIGを引き起こすこともあります。
sensitive
センシティブ
It's probably as simple as this
おそらくこれと同じくらい簡単です
And it's usually possible to go
そして、通常は行くことができます
Really have an allergic reaction to this allergist when it bothers you a lot
それがあなたをとても悩ませるとき、このアレルギー専門医に対して本当にアレルギー反応を起こします
You can take a test to see which allergies you are allergic to
自分がどのアレルギーに該当するかを検査で調べることができます
is an allergic reaction
アレルギー反応です
It can also help you do some tests for general immunology and epidemiology
また、一般的な免疫学や疫学の検査を行うのにも役立ちます。
As mentioned earlier, some people are allergic to
先ほども書きましたが、アレルギーを持っている人もいます。
But some people most people don't
しかし、一部の人はそうではありません
So everyone's physique is different
だから身体は人それぞれ違うんです
here is another question please
別の質問がありますのでお願いします
Thanks
ありがとう
I'm sorry, Director Liu, does liver muscle function have anything to do with allergies?
申し訳ありませんが、リュー所長、肝臓の筋肉機能はアレルギーと関係がありますか?
The second question is to say
2番目の質問はこう言うことです
Recently, someone commented that eating good bacteria, probiotics or bacteria
最近、誰かが、善玉菌、プロバイオティクス、細菌を食べることは良いとコメントしました。
So does this good bacteria help reduce allergies?
では、この善玉菌はアレルギーを軽減するのに役立つのでしょうか？
Thanks
ありがとう
I'm not sure about the allergy just now.
アレルギーについては今のところ分かりません。
I think this about our human body
私たちの人間の体についてこう思います
It's the systemic symptoms I just talked about
それは先ほど話した全身症状です
So I can't say that what I do will not affect other people.
だから、自分のやっていることが他の人に影響を与えないとは言えません。
I think it is possible
可能だと思います
But I can't think of any information on this
しかし、これに関する情報は思いつきません
As for what you just said, it is
あなたが今言ったことに関して言えば、それは
I guess if I only know what's right it's
正しいことだけを知っていればそれが正しいと思う
Like things like Lexlectropacillus
Lexlectropacillus のようなもの
that's what i asked me to write
それが私に書くように頼んだものです
thought I just mentioned that we now
先ほど言ったと思いますが、私たちは今
It seems that the sensitivity is getting more and more, and the allergies are getting more and more
ますます過敏症になっているようで、アレルギーも増えてきています
So why is this like this? There are different theories.
では、なぜこのようになるのでしょうか? さまざまな理論があります。
There's a theory that we're getting cleaner
私たちはきれいになっているという理論がある
So we are the first to go up during development
したがって、開発中に最初に上昇するのは私たちです
we are not exposed to germs
私たちは細菌にさらされていません
Bacteria I just answered a question
バクテリア 質問に答えたところです
I'm making it a little more professional
もう少し専門的にしてみます
That is, we see that the usual response of bacteria is to
つまり、細菌の通常の反応は次のとおりであることがわかります。
Type 1 T cells respond to TH1
1 型 T 細胞は TH1 に応答します
That's what we just said
それが私たちが今言ったことです
For our Ellogy, TH2 is the second type
弊社の Ellogy では、TH2 が 2 番目のタイプです。
If it is your body that produces Type 1
あなたの体がタイプ 1 を生成する場合
The second type will be less like this
2番目のタイプはこれよりも少なくなります
So according to this
したがって、これによると
Just want to say if we let our body come
ただ言いたいのは、体を許したら
to get in touch with this thing like a virus
ウイルスのようなものと接触する
It's bacteria
それは細菌です
Then let's generate a comparison of the first type
次に、最初のタイプの比較を生成しましょう
and just like that
そしてそのまま
there is no second line
2行目はありません
but i guess it's a thought
でもそれは思い込みだと思う
so is it because of this
そうだ、これのせいなのか
just to get some people to start trying this
何人かの人にこれを試し始めてもらうためです
But what this does in this regard is
しかし、この点でこれが何をするかというと、
try a lot
たくさん試してみる
doing this
これをやっている
some seem to work
一部は機能するようです
some don't seem to work
一部は機能しないようです
so no conclusion yet
だからまだ結論は出ていない
Is it possible to use this to treat
これを使って治療することは可能ですか
these allergies
これらのアレルギー
not entirely clear
完全には明らかではない
But this also mentions
しかし、これにも言及されています
Just what I just said is clean
私が今言ったことはきれいなことです
It doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
I just mentioned the skin
先ほど肌のことを言いました
Maybe you didn't imagine
もしかしたら想像していなかったかもしれません
think we have thousands
何千人もいると思う
Thousands of these
何千もの
not thousands
何千ものではありません
but thousands of kinds
でも何千種類も
sexual exercise here
性的練習はここで
Our name is micropeiota
私たちの名前はマイクロピオタです
That's what we do
それが私たちのやることです
the same in the intestines
腸内でも同様
I say this theory
私はこの理論を言います
Put this other this like
これを他のこれにいいね
After eating Lactopacillus
ラクトパチルスを食べた後
will appear to that
そうなるだろう
Those microphone towers inside will affect the
内部のマイクタワーは、
Affect those microphone towers
マイクタワーに影響を与える
Affects our body's immune response
私たちの体の免疫反応に影響を与える
it's amazing so quantum maybe
すごいから量子かもね
Through that relationship it affects this allergy
その関係を通じてこのアレルギーに影響を与えます
Maybe it's a possibility, that comparison is a little more complicated
おそらくその可能性はありますが、その比較はもう少し複雑です
I just mentioned the allergic reaction between SARS and the new arrival
先ほど、SARSと新たな感染者との間のアレルギー反応について触れました。
Then I want to ask now because it has been seen clinically
それから、臨床的に見られたので今聞きたいのですが
Genital cystitis, then I want to ask
性器膀胱炎 そこで聞きたいのですが
This is also related to the allergic reaction
これもアレルギー反応と関係があります
I don't know what this is called
これを何と呼ぶのか分かりません
how are you explaining
どうやって説明してるの？
TiCa then genital cystitis
TiCa、その後性器膀胱炎
Long-term is like cystitis
長期的には膀胱炎になるよ
you're thinking about that
あなたはそれについて考えています
Yes, just name it
はい、名前だけ付けてください
I don't think that has anything to do with allergies
アレルギーとは関係ないと思います
it doesn't matter, yes
関係ありません、はい
It has nothing to do with the so-called allergies
いわゆるアレルギーとは関係ありません
But what you say must matter
でも、あなたの言うことは重要なはずです
speaking is relevant
話すことは関係がある
next question, come on, please
次の質問、どうぞ。
that is
あれは
microphone, click
マイク、クリック
green
緑
May I?
いいですか？
I want to ask the director
監督に聞きたい
Because I am a student of Xinzhuang Shixiep University
私は新荘市磧大学の学生なので
two are
二人は
Come to politics after surgery
手術後は政界に復帰
After surgery, my hand now often
手術後、私の手は頻繁に
the forearm often speaks
前腕はよく話します
If there is one more symptom before the speech, it will occur first
スピーチの前にもう 1 つの症状がある場合、それが最初に発生します
eruption
汗泡疹
Sweat herpes followed by speech
発汗ヘルペスとその後の発声
I want to ask
聞きたいです
this
これ
that sweat herpes is
その汗ヘルペスは
how
どうやって
how and why happened
どのように、そしてなぜ起こったのか
how to reduce how often it happens
それが起こる頻度を減らす方法
Then keep doing this many times, will it affect
その後、これを何度も繰り返しますが、影響はありますか?
Please bring up other sequelae
他の後遺症もあげてください
Thanks
ありがとう
Sorry, my Chinese is not very clear
申し訳ありませんが、私の中国語はあまり明確ではありません。
Han Leopard Clinic
漢豹診
Herbis bar
ハービスバー
English is
英語は
there is now
現在就有
have it now
今すぐ持ってください
Han Leopard Clinic
漢豹診
no
いいえ
wait and see how you are
様子を見て待ってください
right
右
I need to know more now
今すぐもっと知る必要があります
I want to ask the director
監督に聞きたい
I'm a high school student at Yan Ping Middle School
私は延平中学校の高校生です。
I am very interested in biology
私は生物学にとても興味があります
I read it in my school biology textbook
学校の生物の教科書で読んだ
When pathogens invade the human body
病原体が人体に侵入すると
The human immune system can
人間の免疫システムは、
Thousands of B cells, NT cells
数千のB細胞、NT細胞
Select the one corresponding to the pathogen to deal with him
彼に対処する病原体に対応するものを選択してください
Then what I want to ask the director is
そこで監督に聞きたいのは、
How to choose the human immune system
人間の免疫システムを選択する方法
Thanks
ありがとう
I think your enough is probably a function of extremely strong cells
あなたは十分だと思います、おそらく非常に強い細胞の働きです
I just said that the extremely strong cells are the last generals
非常に強い細胞が最後の将軍だと言ったばかりです
He'll tear viruses or foreign matter into it.
ウイルスや異物を引き裂きます。
Then he'll come back out
そしたら彼はまた出てくるよ
Then this makes the T cell the T cell just mentioned
これにより、T 細胞が先ほど述べた T 細胞になります。
At the beginning of the T cells, there is no need to know what will affect them
最初は、T 細胞自体は自分に何が影響するかを知る必要はありません。
but he will put this
でも彼はこれを置くでしょう
So I just said above what kind of antigen is the cell that presents the antigen
さて、上で抗原を提示する細胞がどのような抗原であるかを述べました。
Energy Presented Cell
エネルギー提示セル
He will let T cells Educate
彼はT細胞に教育させます
Only then will the T cells know
そうして初めてT細胞は知ることができる
He will have an effect on that antigen
彼はその抗原に影響を与えるだろう
Therefore, there was no exposure to this antigen at all.
したがって、この抗原への曝露はまったくありませんでした。
T cells are all the same
T細胞はどれも同じ
But after the extremely strong cells penetrate this source
しかし、非常に強力な細胞が発生源に侵入した後、
it just shows up
それはただ現れるだけです
Then let the T cell know which source it should look at
次に、T 細胞にどのソースを調べるべきかを知らせます。
such a selection process
このような選択プロセス
In other words, there are mathematical types of T cells to choose from.
言い換えれば、選択できる T 細胞には数学的な種類があるということです。
Rather, let certain cells
むしろ、特定の細胞を
adicate becomes that it can respond to that look at the source
adicate はソースを見てそれに応答できるようになります
The same goes for B cells
B細胞も同様です
There was another question here just now, is it gone?
先ほどここで別の質問がありましたが、もうなくなりましたか？
is there any problem
何か問題ある
ok our last question
はい、最後の質問です
Ask our Deputy Director Li
副所長の李さんに聞いてください
Because you are also an expert in dermatology
皮膚科の専門医でもあるので
we have a friend
私たちには友達がいます
his skin
彼の肌
not clean
きれいではない
One piece of white, one piece of white on the face and hands
白1枚、顔と手に白1枚
Seen by many dermatologists
多くの皮膚科医が診ています
I want to ask the director
監督に聞きたい
What is his disease and what is the cause?
彼の病気は何ですか、またその原因は何ですか?
what's the difference
違いは何ですか
Thanks
ありがとう
see must
必見です
Are you talking about white spots?
白い斑点のことを言っているのでしょうか？
White spot is called Bertar Ligo in English
ホワイトスポットは英語でBertar Ligoと呼ばれます。
Yes, Bertar Ligo
はい、ベルタル・リゴです
that words
その言葉
not so easy to control
コントロールするのはそれほど簡単ではありません
But the same goes for the liver, for example.
しかし、これは例えば肝臓にも当てはまります。
illumination, illumination light
照光,照外線光
can treat most
ほとんどの治療が可能
Where do some medicines look
いくつかの薬はどこにありますか
some medicine can rub
薬によってはこすれる可能性があります
In some cases, it responds quite well
場合によってはかなり良く反応する
right
右
He sees various dermatologists
色々な皮膚科を受診している
I read a lot and didn't think about it
たくさん読んだけど何も考えなかった
served
提供されました
Then the other one is
それからもう一つは、
A relatively new development is
比較的新しい展開としては、
He wants cell transplantation, so it becomes stem cells
彼は細胞移植を望んでいます、それでそれは幹細胞になります
This is because his rate of fire cells don't
これは、彼のファイアセルの速度がそうでないためです。
So if you say it's pancreas
それで膵臓だと言ったら
he can recover
彼は回復できる
so that is a way
それは方法です
For example, if the scope of influence is too large
例えば影響範囲が広すぎる場合
It's not conspiracy
陰謀じゃないよ
but later development
しかしその後の展開
maybe from the dry bag perspective
おそらくドライバッグの観点から
just some people will react
一部の人だけが反応するだろう
some people will have
持っている人もいるでしょう
Just two is one on steroids
ちょうど 2 つはステロイドを使用した 1 つです
something else called
別の何かと呼ばれるもの
The product name in English is called Protopic
英語での商品名はProtopicといいます。
Protopic
プロトピック
The director finally asks you
監督は最後にあなたに尋ねます
that
それか
Is it related to allergies?
アレルギーと関係があるのでしょうか？
Are you allergic to dermatitis?
皮膚炎にアレルギーがありますか?
Significant dermatitis is skin
重大な皮膚炎は皮膚です
also considered allergic
也算過敏
Thanks
ありがとう
So what is being said is
それで、言われているのは、
To spot this part
この部分を見つけるには
this is small
これは小さいです
it's about the wife
それは妻のことです
too sun
太陽が多すぎる
He said it was more serious
彼はもっと深刻だと言いました
bigger
より大きい
This intentional eye relationship
この意図的な目の関係
right
右
Generally
一般的
this may be
これはそうかもしれない
it's not easy
簡単ではない
He also said no
彼もノーと言った
good
良い
we again
私たちはまた
Thank you Chief Liu
劉長官、ありがとう
wonderful speech
素晴らしいスピーチ
That
それか
give me one last minute
最後に少し時間をください
That's what we learned in December
それが私たちが12月に学んだことです
want to test
テストしたい
is up to us
それは私たち次第です
China Cultural Responsibility Institute's
中國文責研究所的
Governance
ガバナンス
The researcher wants to speak
研究者は話したい
Our Vernacular Bible
私たちの現地語聖書
is a rather interesting subject
かなり興味深いテーマです
so the time is in
それで、時間は
December 25th
12月25日
Tuesday night
火曜の晩
also in this place
この場所にも
to give a speech
スピーチをする
All are welcome to participate
ぜひご参加ください
Thanks
ありがとう